6 WORDTAG O mind
5 WORDTAG O 416
31 WORDTAG I-PER Peter
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Western
16 WORDTAG O event
6 WORDTAG O briefing
60 WORDTAG I-LOC United
9 WORDTAG O maybe
13 WORDTAG O 82
26 WORDTAG O 55
6 WORDTAG O mate
12 WORDTAG O cow
7 WORDTAG O prix
6 WORDTAG I-PER Stephane
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Old
9 WORDTAG O reduce
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Taibe
61 WORDTAG O run
10 WORDTAG O clocked
36 WORDTAG O wickets
35 WORDTAG O started
80 WORDTAG O during
41 WORDTAG I-MISC LEAGUE
84 WORDTAG O still
6 WORDTAG I-PER Fredericks
1 WORDTAG I-ORG BP
716 WORDTAG O by
8 WORDTAG O FORECAST
16 WORDTAG I-ORG DETROIT
8 WORDTAG O animal
10 WORDTAG O suffering
16 WORDTAG O 10,000
49 WORDTAG I-MISC League
7 WORDTAG I-PER De
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Ocean
23 WORDTAG I-LOC Mexico
1 WORDTAG I-MISC News
13 WORDTAG I-MISC Prix
16 WORDTAG O walked
48 WORDTAG I-ORG National
3 WORDTAG I-PER Liu
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Iranian
53 WORDTAG O security
27 WORDTAG O violence
392 WORDTAG O 5
5 WORDTAG I-PER Allen
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Rotterdam
5 WORDTAG O arrangements
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Northampton
9 WORDTAG O scientific
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Gabon
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Sierra
7 WORDTAG I-PER Gooch
12 WORDTAG O history
9 WORDTAG I-MISC Taleban
17 WORDTAG O thought
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Brann
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Tamil
1 WORDTAG I-ORG party
13 WORDTAG I-PER Salim
15 WORDTAG O published
1 WORDTAG O Medical
6 WORDTAG I-PER Eefje
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Goldman
5 WORDTAG O links
55 WORDTAG I-MISC European
5 WORDTAG O Parliament
46 WORDTAG O ahead
1 WORDTAG I-ORG HONG
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Kabul
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Shanghai
5 WORDTAG O businessman
45 WORDTAG O hours
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Times
5 WORDTAG O showers
13 WORDTAG O 6-
1 WORDTAG B-MISC Cup
17 WORDTAG O looked
1 WORDTAG I-PER Park
51 WORDTAG O miles
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Pakistan
5 WORDTAG I-MISC No
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Neuchatel
6 WORDTAG I-ORG ETA
12 WORDTAG O cattle
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Enschede
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Cofinec
1 WORDTAG O Bank
12 WORDTAG O boost
35 WORDTAG O champions
5 WORDTAG I-ORG IMED
13 WORDTAG O unable
8 WORDTAG O autonomy
4 WORDTAG I-ORG DE
5 WORDTAG O settlements
5 WORDTAG O Q2
24 WORDTAG O step
73 WORDTAG I-LOC NEW
48 WORDTAG O several
23 WORDTAG I-LOC Costa
1 WORDTAG I-MISC convention
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Nantes
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Saskatchewan
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Larnaca
9 WORDTAG O stable
4 WORDTAG I-LOC Toronto
37 WORDTAG O 9.
65 WORDTAG O league
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Bremen
5 WORDTAG O Seven
1 WORDTAG I-PER Boston
5 WORDTAG O shelling
4 WORDTAG I-LOC .
5 WORDTAG O producers
18 WORDTAG O debt
6 WORDTAG O education
1 WORDTAG I-PER N.J.
6 WORDTAG O terrorist
5 WORDTAG I-PER Boer
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Bangkok
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Blackpool
6 WORDTAG I-PER Erik
22 WORDTAG I-MISC Swiss
16 WORDTAG I-PER Carlos
7 WORDTAG I-LOC JAKARTA
10 WORDTAG O provincial
3390 WORDTAG O in
15 WORDTAG O State
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Chelsea
11 WORDTAG O improve
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Globo
16 WORDTAG O common
81 WORDTAG O season
5 WORDTAG O re-election
26 WORDTAG O keep
1 WORDTAG I-LOC &
6 WORDTAG O engineering
15 WORDTAG O remain
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Athens
5 WORDTAG O sealed
2994 WORDTAG O a
12 WORDTAG I-LOC Middle
27 WORDTAG O levels
13 WORDTAG O numbers
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Huddersfield
18 WORDTAG O doing
14 WORDTAG O activity
9 WORDTAG O hitting
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Indonesia
3 WORDTAG I-MISC Labour
6 WORDTAG O 7.5
5 WORDTAG O intends
8 WORDTAG O Her
12 WORDTAG I-MISC Islamist
6 WORDTAG I-PER O'Neill
51 WORDTAG O drawn
27 WORDTAG O making
23 WORDTAG O armed
8 WORDTAG I-MISC the
46 WORDTAG I-PER M.
7 WORDTAG I-MISC GRAND
43 WORDTAG O agreement
15 WORDTAG O rugby
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Hampshire
1 WORDTAG I-ORG One
42 WORDTAG O away
5 WORDTAG I-PER Gephardt
7 WORDTAG O 3.8
6 WORDTAG O dn
17 WORDTAG I-ORG ST
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Socialist
34 WORDTAG I-MISC South
10 WORDTAG O additional
1 WORDTAG I-MISC no
25 WORDTAG O problem
9 WORDTAG I-PER Hingis
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Miss
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Bombay
4 WORDTAG I-PER Taylor
3 WORDTAG O interior
10 WORDTAG I-ORG NAC
40 WORDTAG O c
15 WORDTAG O either
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Austria
7 WORDTAG O asylum
5 WORDTAG O pulp
10 WORDTAG I-PER Rafter
12 WORDTAG O 79
43 WORDTAG O plans
12 WORDTAG I-ORG Hamburg
5 WORDTAG O Financial
19 WORDTAG O sign
53 WORDTAG O agreed
6 WORDTAG O operator
14 WORDTAG O interim
12 WORDTAG O hijacked
5 WORDTAG O Only
9 WORDTAG I-PER Carl
12 WORDTAG O income
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Basque
1 WORDTAG O Mother
1 WORDTAG I-ORG is
40 WORDTAG I-ORG Union
21 WORDTAG O sector
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Palace
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Basque
8 WORDTAG O treated
10 WORDTAG O 3,000
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Red
9 WORDTAG O failure
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Williams
5 WORDTAG O dozens
18 WORDTAG I-PER Christie
18 WORDTAG O range
6 WORDTAG O highest
8 WORDTAG O construction
11 WORDTAG I-PER Tony
14 WORDTAG O seeking
11 WORDTAG I-PER Fox
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Council
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Oldham
17 WORDTAG O output
291 WORDTAG O out
5 WORDTAG O 1999
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Athletics
34 WORDTAG O planned
12 WORDTAG O progress
1 WORDTAG I-MISC 21st
5 WORDTAG O bush
8 WORDTAG O 160
57 WORDTAG O cents
26 WORDTAG O Halftime
16 WORDTAG O programme
25 WORDTAG I-LOC Grozny
368 WORDTAG O been
389 WORDTAG O but
5 WORDTAG O aviation
8 WORDTAG I-MISC Gulf
8 WORDTAG O wrist
5 WORDTAG O searched
9 WORDTAG O consumers
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Metro
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Wimbledon
6 WORDTAG O cargoes
10 WORDTAG O pitch
9 WORDTAG O fine
25 WORDTAG O full
7 WORDTAG O hot
29 WORDTAG O action
9 WORDTAG O let
8 WORDTAG O slipped
10 WORDTAG O begun
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Nazi
6 WORDTAG O beating
12 WORDTAG O sheep
6 WORDTAG O crop
105 WORDTAG O statement
8 WORDTAG I-PER Nick
26 WORDTAG O senior
6 WORDTAG O motion
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Expos
6 WORDTAG O intent
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Colorado
51 WORDTAG O refugees
5 WORDTAG I-PER Drew
31 WORDTAG O forced
5 WORDTAG O incumbent
92 WORDTAG O any
137 WORDTAG O We
31 WORDTAG O opening
9 WORDTAG O three-game
6 WORDTAG O bids
16 WORDTAG O YR
8 WORDTAG O acquisition
4 WORDTAG I-ORG France
11 WORDTAG I-PER Ruutel
3 WORDTAG I-MISC Hong
12 WORDTAG O spending
10 WORDTAG O B
28 WORDTAG O analysts
44 WORDTAG O higher
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Peace
6 WORDTAG I-PER Edgar
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Leicester
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Namibia
17 WORDTAG I-PER Philippoussis
5 WORDTAG I-PER Olivier
6 WORDTAG I-ORG .
7 WORDTAG O else
18 WORDTAG O jail
199 WORDTAG O told
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Bratislava
8 WORDTAG O controllers
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Commonwealth
5 WORDTAG O Not
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Paulo
57 WORDTAG O race
8 WORDTAG I-LOC Sakai
6 WORDTAG O 170
525 WORDTAG O be
6 WORDTAG O displayed
5 WORDTAG O semifinal
7 WORDTAG O 120
5 WORDTAG I-PER Novotna
5 WORDTAG O civilian
8 WORDTAG O happened
117 WORDTAG O four
26 WORDTAG O One
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Neths
21 WORDTAG O 36
17 WORDTAG O spokeswoman
24 WORDTAG O leg
9 WORDTAG O registered
8 WORDTAG I-MISC Rally
7 WORDTAG O consider
7 WORDTAG O marketing
8 WORDTAG O confident
8 WORDTAG I-PER Edberg
9 WORDTAG I-PER Owens
5 WORDTAG O tunnel
12 WORDTAG O MATCH
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Minnesota
17 WORDTAG O leaving
5 WORDTAG O realised
11 WORDTAG O living
1 WORDTAG I-ORG self-rule
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Padres
8 WORDTAG I-PER Masterkova
9 WORDTAG O individual
5 WORDTAG O MOTOR
19 WORDTAG O 57
6 WORDTAG O expects
19 WORDTAG O saw
9 WORDTAG O jump
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Zurich
13 WORDTAG I-ORG Lancashire
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Finland
7 WORDTAG O owner
33 WORDTAG O yet
23 WORDTAG O Played
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Ross
8 WORDTAG O begins
6 WORDTAG I-PER Jana
9 WORDTAG O vehicles
5 WORDTAG O 398
5 WORDTAG O consulate
5 WORDTAG I-MISC ADRs
3 WORDTAG I-PER Lincoln
10 WORDTAG O separatists
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Hampshire
16 WORDTAG I-MISC WESTERN
8 WORDTAG O +3
9 WORDTAG O carried
15 WORDTAG I-PER Mike
9 WORDTAG O mainly
12 WORDTAG I-MISC 95
4 WORDTAG I-MISC Super
7 WORDTAG O Ambassador
30 WORDTAG I-LOC PARIS
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Legia
7 WORDTAG O fund
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Rugby
63 WORDTAG O leader
5 WORDTAG O tries
4 WORDTAG I-LOC MONTREAL
1 WORDTAG I-ORG MILAN
25 WORDTAG O health
8 WORDTAG I-PER Coetzer
2 WORDTAG I-ORG School
12 WORDTAG O minority
13 WORDTAG O 61-2
687 WORDTAG O :
8 WORDTAG I-ORG II
18 WORDTAG I-ORG Borussia
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Merrill
18 WORDTAG O rounds
22 WORDTAG O young
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Barrick
5 WORDTAG O CALL
1 WORDTAG I-PER North
9 WORDTAG I-PER Kenneth
5 WORDTAG I-PER Ata-ur-Rehman
10 WORDTAG I-MISC Olympics
5 WORDTAG O Queen
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Helens
2 WORDTAG I-PER Golf
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Thai
5 WORDTAG I-MISC F
536 WORDTAG O not
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Palmans
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Names
15 WORDTAG O property
5 WORDTAG O mining
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Guinea
9 WORDTAG I-PER Costas
39 WORDTAG O nine
2 WORDTAG I-MISC 150
8 WORDTAG I-PER Jacques
25 WORDTAG O 58
13 WORDTAG I-MISC Greek
7 WORDTAG O continuing
6 WORDTAG I-PER King
5 WORDTAG O 600,000
6 WORDTAG O halt
9 WORDTAG O department
260 WORDTAG O one
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Dealers
1 WORDTAG O Wheat
17 WORDTAG O terms
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Dortmund
20 WORDTAG O become
9 WORDTAG O allegedly
10 WORDTAG I-LOC Kashmir
30 WORDTAG O point
32 WORDTAG I-MISC Moslem
34 WORDTAG O production
17 WORDTAG O separatist
12 WORDTAG O suspended
6 WORDTAG O related
10 WORDTAG I-MISC Pakistani
13 WORDTAG I-ORG The
18 WORDTAG O presidential
5 WORDTAG O Up
282 WORDTAG O last
9 WORDTAG O federation
2 WORDTAG O National
3 WORDTAG I-PER McCarthy
15 WORDTAG O sought
180 WORDTAG O about
5 WORDTAG O TOTAL
37 WORDTAG O seen
346 WORDTAG O their
11 WORDTAG O cannot
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Sussex
19 WORDTAG O 1,000
22 WORDTAG O 1992
52 WORDTAG O Attendance
75 WORDTAG O minutes
6 WORDTAG O surge
12 WORDTAG I-PER Stephen
6 WORDTAG O critics
20 WORDTAG O expect
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Crystal
61 WORDTAG O newsroom
18 WORDTAG O stated
12 WORDTAG O score
930 WORDTAG O 3
20 WORDTAG O quiet
5 WORDTAG O prayer
23 WORDTAG O never
6 WORDTAG O wo
15 WORDTAG O nothing
13 WORDTAG O pressure
12 WORDTAG O bit
8 WORDTAG O room
133 WORDTAG I-LOC Britain
11 WORDTAG O 15-10
7 WORDTAG I-PER Judith
201 WORDTAG O three
10 WORDTAG O vice
9 WORDTAG I-MISC Bundesliga
11 WORDTAG O monitors
2 WORDTAG O Investors
9 WORDTAG O 95
6 WORDTAG O amid
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Warsaw
16 WORDTAG O majority
25 WORDTAG I-ORG OSCE
5 WORDTAG I-PER Moxon
13 WORDTAG O interview
5 WORDTAG I-PER Fowler
5 WORDTAG O barred
28 WORDTAG O prison
14 WORDTAG O introduced
27 WORDTAG O within
5 WORDTAG O scoreless
11 WORDTAG O militants
17 WORDTAG O along
3 WORDTAG O Key
6 WORDTAG O Aggregate
5 WORDTAG O 8520
15 WORDTAG I-ORG COLORADO
8 WORDTAG I-ORG RUGBY
112 WORDTAG O five
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Zimbabwe
6 WORDTAG O becoming
3 WORDTAG I-LOC University
37 WORDTAG O working
5 WORDTAG O exiled
6 WORDTAG O fails
25 WORDTAG O continue
6 WORDTAG O offset
6 WORDTAG I-MISC Nikkei
6 WORDTAG O increasing
32 WORDTAG O If
8 WORDTAG I-PER Nathalie
7 WORDTAG O installed
10 WORDTAG O customers
5 WORDTAG I-PER Villeneuve
11 WORDTAG O protection
125 WORDTAG O only
11 WORDTAG O doctors
6 WORDTAG I-PER Kimiko
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Twins
14 WORDTAG I-PER Muster
6 WORDTAG O 10-15
2 WORDTAG I-ORG US
22 WORDTAG O protest
14 WORDTAG O guerrilla
9 WORDTAG O SUMMARY
6 WORDTAG I-PER Takemura
11 WORDTAG O status
5 WORDTAG O parent
6 WORDTAG O picture
17 WORDTAG O demanding
19 WORDTAG O bought
6 WORDTAG I-PER Lawrie
5 WORDTAG O 599
48 WORDTAG O many
6 WORDTAG O DATE
9 WORDTAG I-PER Reagan
132 WORDTAG O SOCCER
5 WORDTAG O pesetas
14 WORDTAG O crew
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Ivorian
9 WORDTAG O Their
5 WORDTAG O laws
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Leverkusen
8 WORDTAG I-PER Knight
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Atlanta
11 WORDTAG I-PER Wilson
8 WORDTAG O difficulties
39 WORDTAG O growth
4 WORDTAG I-LOC MILAN
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Women
5 WORDTAG I-MISC GTR
142 WORDTAG I-LOC Germany
10 WORDTAG O three-run
16 WORDTAG O voters
11 WORDTAG O feet
15 WORDTAG I-PER Tim
30 WORDTAG O law
15 WORDTAG O hour
2 WORDTAG I-PER Charlton
6 WORDTAG O minimum
930 WORDTAG O at
7 WORDTAG O versus
25 WORDTAG O wife
6 WORDTAG O 15-9
11 WORDTAG O lawyer
15 WORDTAG O kidnapped
5 WORDTAG O Since
2 WORDTAG O TIMES
14 WORDTAG O qualifying
15 WORDTAG O administration
7 WORDTAG O failing
5 WORDTAG I-PER Alain
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Assembly
5 WORDTAG O attributable
12 WORDTAG I-ORG USDA
9 WORDTAG O captured
14 WORDTAG O walk
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Bonds
98 WORDTAG I-LOC Italy
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Mapei
7 WORDTAG I-PER Walker
4 WORDTAG I-LOC 's
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Taylor
306 WORDTAG O its
8 WORDTAG I-PER Fernando
5 WORDTAG O skilled
14 WORDTAG O GAMES
6 WORDTAG I-PER Michelle
8 WORDTAG O unc
5 WORDTAG O tell
23 WORDTAG O investors
5 WORDTAG I-LOC MADRID
4 WORDTAG O Armed
59 WORDTAG O lower
22 WORDTAG I-PER D.
11 WORDTAG O advantage
6 WORDTAG O ratio
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Banespa
5 WORDTAG O shr
1 WORDTAG O SOUTH
5 WORDTAG I-PER Arnold
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Gold
10 WORDTAG O effective
5 WORDTAG O pursue
41 WORDTAG O north
97 WORDTAG O August
8 WORDTAG O accord
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Greens
5 WORDTAG I-PER Ekeus
38 WORDTAG I-LOC Austria
40 WORDTAG O major
6 WORDTAG I-PER Damm
1 WORDTAG I-MISC against
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Brisbane
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Edouard
12 WORDTAG I-MISC Irish
13 WORDTAG O address
47 WORDTAG O 17
5 WORDTAG I-PER Frankie
6 WORDTAG O outbreak
5 WORDTAG O 1980
5 WORDTAG O photographs
5 WORDTAG I-PER Krajicek
5 WORDTAG O exclusive
10 WORDTAG O headquarters
11 WORDTAG O reserve
7 WORDTAG I-PER Woosnam
10 WORDTAG O existing
5 WORDTAG I-PER Magnus
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Maoist
70 WORDTAG O most
11 WORDTAG O ever
7 WORDTAG O hog
7 WORDTAG O avoided
19 WORDTAG O tender
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Baker
1 WORDTAG I-ORG KONG
8 WORDTAG I-PER Iliescu
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Workers
149 WORDTAG O before
17 WORDTAG I-ORG News
7 WORDTAG O moisture
3 WORDTAG I-MISC GOLF
1 WORDTAG I-MISC San
11 WORDTAG O marks
13 WORDTAG O unq
4 WORDTAG O Human
6 WORDTAG I-ORG SK
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Francisco
10 WORDTAG I-LOC Serbia
2 WORDTAG I-MISC winners
6 WORDTAG O shared
5 WORDTAG I-PER Pires
1 WORDTAG O Daily
5 WORDTAG I-LOC MINNESOTA
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Montreal
17 WORDTAG O your
1 WORDTAG B-MISC East
10 WORDTAG O crash
20 WORDTAG O always
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Football
12 WORDTAG O daughter
6 WORDTAG I-MISC Dow
11 WORDTAG O below
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Bill
13 WORDTAG O However
16 WORDTAG I-MISC EASTERN
5 WORDTAG O accusing
106 WORDTAG O day
32 WORDTAG O tabulate
10 WORDTAG I-LOC ATHENS
3 WORDTAG B-MISC Grand
12 WORDTAG O ambassador
52 WORDTAG O going
9 WORDTAG O ballot
471 WORDTAG O after
8 WORDTAG I-PER Mika
6 WORDTAG O 15.
1 WORDTAG I-MISC 11
52 WORDTAG O 73
38 WORDTAG O total
15 WORDTAG O invited
13 WORDTAG O ?
19 WORDTAG O traffic
45 WORDTAG O weeks
2 WORDTAG O West
6 WORDTAG O 33rd
18 WORDTAG O commission
6 WORDTAG O suspension
2 WORDTAG I-MISC People
10 WORDTAG O ends
2 WORDTAG B-MISC GRAND
7 WORDTAG O 5-2
21 WORDTAG O settlement
17 WORDTAG O attempt
21 WORDTAG O 34
6 WORDTAG O oppose
5 WORDTAG O .469
7 WORDTAG I-PER Koerts
24 WORDTAG O Result
9 WORDTAG O opponents
33 WORDTAG I-MISC Kurdish
5 WORDTAG O outcome
10 WORDTAG O suit
3 WORDTAG O Workers
15 WORDTAG O Last
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Institute
6 WORDTAG O grounds
6 WORDTAG O inch
5 WORDTAG O END
1 WORDTAG I-LOC WESTERN
1 WORDTAG I-PER Windows
9 WORDTAG O fellow
11 WORDTAG O alleged
5 WORDTAG O gives
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Washington
5 WORDTAG O ARA
7 WORDTAG O virus
5 WORDTAG O 1-2
37 WORDTAG O ---
9 WORDTAG O example
4 WORDTAG I-PER Lehman
63 WORDTAG I-LOC Israel
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Tennis
17 WORDTAG O husband
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Social
5 WORDTAG O trained
17 WORDTAG I-ORG Manchester
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Stock
13 WORDTAG I-ORG First
6 WORDTAG O relatively
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Breda
11 WORDTAG O tests
24 WORDTAG O stage
16 WORDTAG O finished
5 WORDTAG I-PER Tang
8 WORDTAG I-PER Thompson
13 WORDTAG I-ORG Texas
6 WORDTAG O 180
26 WORDTAG O inning
24 WORDTAG O paper
21 WORDTAG I-LOC Colombia
16 WORDTAG I-MISC Democrats
10 WORDTAG O crashed
5 WORDTAG O recover
22 WORDTAG I-MISC Polish
6 WORDTAG I-PER Ischinger
5 WORDTAG O supported
8 WORDTAG O produced
10 WORDTAG O 37
9 WORDTAG O rural
19 WORDTAG O allowing
11 WORDTAG O scandal
9 WORDTAG I-PER Stefan
8 WORDTAG O places
23 WORDTAG O 32
16 WORDTAG O vouch
314 WORDTAG O up
2 WORDTAG I-MISC de
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Airways
7 WORDTAG I-PER Mohamed
6 WORDTAG O arriving
12 WORDTAG I-PER Crawley
10 WORDTAG O powers
21 WORDTAG I-LOC ENGLAND
4 WORDTAG O Hurricane
9 WORDTAG O shipment
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Football
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Foreign
8 WORDTAG O became
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Hungary
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Dole
3 WORDTAG I-LOC LOUIS
33 WORDTAG I-LOC Slovakia
11 WORDTAG O draft
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Tamils
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Holdings
8 WORDTAG O SUMMARIES
1 WORDTAG B-MISC Iraqi
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Gloucestershire
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Pakistani
16 WORDTAG O diplomatic
44 WORDTAG O vs
13 WORDTAG O raised
6 WORDTAG I-PER Roberto
28 WORDTAG O 6-0
11 WORDTAG I-LOC Jamaica
5 WORDTAG O tested
7 WORDTAG O attacked
5 WORDTAG O caps
44 WORDTAG O 18
37 WORDTAG O hold
12 WORDTAG O moved
15 WORDTAG O championships
8 WORDTAG O comments
13 WORDTAG O conflict
5 WORDTAG O isolated
11 WORDTAG O airports
9 WORDTAG O outstanding
6 WORDTAG O lb
7 WORDTAG O **
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Taipei
20 WORDTAG O weapons
14 WORDTAG O unrest
9 WORDTAG O slow
17 WORDTAG O development
7 WORDTAG O everything
20 WORDTAG O dropped
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Roosevelt
8 WORDTAG O abortion
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Bolton
5 WORDTAG O aggressive
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Armed
1 WORDTAG B-MISC World
5 WORDTAG I-PER God
5 WORDTAG O drivers
37 WORDTAG O PCT
20 WORDTAG O mark
5 WORDTAG O camps
2 WORDTAG I-LOC and
4 WORDTAG I-PER Lynch
24 WORDTAG O according
20 WORDTAG I-LOC BONN
26 WORDTAG O services
7 WORDTAG O labour
7 WORDTAG O faced
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Mother
6 WORDTAG O jewelry
8 WORDTAG O militia
10 WORDTAG O advertising
25 WORDTAG O centre
8 WORDTAG O casualties
7 WORDTAG O 16.
4 WORDTAG I-PER Christopher
29 WORDTAG O level
8 WORDTAG O Amount
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Democrats
10 WORDTAG I-LOC UK
5 WORDTAG O investments
1 WORDTAG O Capital
8 WORDTAG O capacity
7 WORDTAG I-PER Bhutto
6 WORDTAG O taxes
6 WORDTAG B-ORG FDP
6 WORDTAG O exile
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Los
7 WORDTAG O decisions
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Reserve
13 WORDTAG I-ORG Information
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Zabrze
5 WORDTAG O [
5 WORDTAG O bases
5 WORDTAG O congress
6 WORDTAG O affairs
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Atlantic
840 WORDTAG O with
7 WORDTAG I-PER Lindsay
7 WORDTAG O Its
8 WORDTAG O cotton
7 WORDTAG O possibly
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Istanbul
6 WORDTAG O rider
7 WORDTAG O founded
6 WORDTAG O tourist
5 WORDTAG O swimming
15 WORDTAG I-PER Ijaz
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Leduc
7 WORDTAG O certainly
6 WORDTAG O forecasts
5 WORDTAG O pace
6 WORDTAG O signal
71 WORDTAG I-LOC India
12 WORDTAG O whom
14 WORDTAG I-PER Mickelson
4 WORDTAG O My
45 WORDTAG O came
6 WORDTAG O boosted
6 WORDTAG O contribute
13 WORDTAG O industrial
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Battle
55 WORDTAG I-MISC American
13 WORDTAG I-ORG Eindhoven
25 WORDTAG I-ORG PUK
5 WORDTAG O paedophile
9 WORDTAG O nearby
6 WORDTAG O compensation
8 WORDTAG I-PER Ali
8 WORDTAG O SCOREBOARD
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Antwerp
16 WORDTAG O passenger
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Wolf
6 WORDTAG O Summaries
13 WORDTAG O injuries
14 WORDTAG I-LOC Malaysia
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Arabs
14 WORDTAG O body
6 WORDTAG O love
28 WORDTAG O how
6 WORDTAG I-PER Brad
10 WORDTAG O barrels
35 WORDTAG O us
1 WORDTAG I-MISC 1990
143 WORDTAG O could
8 WORDTAG O Thousands
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Daily
13 WORDTAG O purchase
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Surrey
30 WORDTAG O immediately
8 WORDTAG I-PER Antonio
30 WORDTAG I-ORG CHICAGO
28 WORDTAG I-PER Mushtaq
14 WORDTAG O auction
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Sale
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Canberra
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Field
10 WORDTAG O SECOND
7 WORDTAG O partners
12 WORDTAG O welfare
16 WORDTAG I-PER C.
1 WORDTAG I-PER Florence
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Johnson
4 WORDTAG I-ORG TIMES
2 WORDTAG I-MISC 's
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Bulgarian
17 WORDTAG O difficult
15 WORDTAG O protests
19 WORDTAG O governor
29 WORDTAG O process
11 WORDTAG I-PER Andre
8 WORDTAG O 30,000
7 WORDTAG O agenda
49 WORDTAG I-ORG Corp
5 WORDTAG I-PER Rangarajan
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Belgrade
1 WORDTAG B-MISC COUNTY
8 WORDTAG O gathering
1 WORDTAG O Social
6 WORDTAG O die
5 WORDTAG O appearance
25 WORDTAG O areas
22 WORDTAG O These
1 WORDTAG B-MISC Atlanta
11 WORDTAG O 7-2
8 WORDTAG O keeping
5 WORDTAG O defenders
1 WORDTAG O Research
5 WORDTAG I-PER Gerhard
9 WORDTAG O success
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Microsoft
6 WORDTAG O pushed
6 WORDTAG I-MISC Avonex
64 WORDTAG O 67
561 WORDTAG O had
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Middle
29 WORDTAG O daily
12 WORDTAG O strategic
7 WORDTAG I-ORG TVM
19 WORDTAG I-PER Meri
19 WORDTAG O release
8 WORDTAG I-LOC Island
19 WORDTAG I-MISC A$
17 WORDTAG O polls
6 WORDTAG O mm
6 WORDTAG O 32.0
6 WORDTAG O monitoring
7 WORDTAG I-PER Pollock
9 WORDTAG O disappointing
531 WORDTAG O were
5 WORDTAG O intensive
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Rwanda
32 WORDTAG O interest
124 WORDTAG O group
5 WORDTAG I-PER Albert
9 WORDTAG I-PER Rios
16 WORDTAG I-LOC Korea
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Kent
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Cleveland
8 WORDTAG O materials
17 WORDTAG I-ORG MINNESOTA
10 WORDTAG O 5,000
7 WORDTAG O fair
6 WORDTAG O 70th
5 WORDTAG O selected
65 WORDTAG O profit
2 WORDTAG O Army
5 WORDTAG O surgeon
9 WORDTAG I-ORG La
10 WORDTAG O fear
12 WORDTAG O 0-1
6 WORDTAG O located
4 WORDTAG I-LOC Houston
8 WORDTAG I-MISC OF
58 WORDTAG I-PER Mark
127 WORDTAG O state
7 WORDTAG I-PER Hussain
9 WORDTAG O Speaker
7 WORDTAG O greatest
6 WORDTAG O bombing
15 WORDTAG I-ORG Lens
76 WORDTAG O party
2 WORDTAG I-PER Spot
16 WORDTAG I-PER Sampras
7 WORDTAG O Earlier
17 WORDTAG I-LOC Cuba
20 WORDTAG O coalition
1 WORDTAG B-MISC Islamic
1 WORDTAG B-LOC High
55 WORDTAG I-PER Michael
16 WORDTAG I-ORG City
31 WORDTAG O received
17 WORDTAG O battle
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Super
18 WORDTAG O murder
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Southend
1095 WORDTAG O was
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Linz
43 WORDTAG I-ORG Bank
7 WORDTAG O items
5 WORDTAG I-PER Kennedy
13 WORDTAG I-ORG Lloyd
3 WORDTAG O Major
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Kiev
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Stadler
10 WORDTAG O film
4 WORDTAG O Company
1 WORDTAG O Best
5 WORDTAG I-LOC SRI
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Luxembourg
8 WORDTAG I-PER Gilbertson
6 WORDTAG O yield
5 WORDTAG I-PER Flower
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Dm
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Hansa
1 WORDTAG I-MISC 76
32 WORDTAG O stock
32 WORDTAG O reports
21 WORDTAG O dealers
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Itar-Tass
6 WORDTAG O targets
11 WORDTAG O suspect
5 WORDTAG O palace
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Braves
9 WORDTAG O midnight
11 WORDTAG O interests
8 WORDTAG O miss
2 WORDTAG B-MISC SUPER
18 WORDTAG O exchange
5 WORDTAG O profitable
14 WORDTAG O 39
6 WORDTAG O colony
74 WORDTAG O 7-6
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Abu
16 WORDTAG I-PER Juan
10 WORDTAG O kill
6 WORDTAG O airliner
8 WORDTAG O recovered
34 WORDTAG I-ORG 's
8 WORDTAG I-LOC Florida
49 WORDTAG I-ORG New
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Taibe
7 WORDTAG O regions
19 WORDTAG I-PER Brady
1 WORDTAG I-PER Houston
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Rio
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Uganda
5 WORDTAG O holds
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Reds
54 WORDTAG O May
21 WORDTAG I-PER Todd
42 WORDTAG O oil
6 WORDTAG O satisfied
7 WORDTAG O Baseball
71 WORDTAG O you
8 WORDTAG O rand
10 WORDTAG I-PER Machado
5 WORDTAG O otherwise
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Surabaya
10 WORDTAG I-PER Johan
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Committee
12 WORDTAG I-ORG Seattle
14 WORDTAG O impact
1 WORDTAG I-ORG High
176 WORDTAG O people
8 WORDTAG O 24th
6 WORDTAG O attempted
29 WORDTAG O contract
8 WORDTAG O shut
55 WORDTAG O 75
9 WORDTAG O right-wing
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Germany
1 WORDTAG I-ORG P
7 WORDTAG O brokers
1 WORDTAG I-MISC is
12 WORDTAG O crisis
13 WORDTAG O bourse
19 WORDTAG O condition
47 WORDTAG O hit
106 WORDTAG O just
15 WORDTAG O eighth
7 WORDTAG O entire
27 WORDTAG I-LOC Chicago
7 WORDTAG O cholesterol
22 WORDTAG O When
33 WORDTAG I-LOC Romania
19 WORDTAG O declined
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Columbia
61 WORDTAG O support
6 WORDTAG O scientist
7 WORDTAG O Home
6 WORDTAG I-PER Turner
4 WORDTAG I-MISC RALLY
42 WORDTAG I-PER Lebed
9 WORDTAG O insurance
9 WORDTAG I-MISC DEM
12 WORDTAG O ATHLETICS
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Roman
6 WORDTAG O 1995/96
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Tibet
5 WORDTAG O bright
1 WORDTAG I-PER Sunday
82 WORDTAG O tonnes
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Street
13 WORDTAG O changed
7 WORDTAG O column
6 WORDTAG I-LOC BUDAPEST
7 WORDTAG O communist
10 WORDTAG O 500
5 WORDTAG O .470
109 WORDTAG O official
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Seattle
18 WORDTAG O 35
55 WORDTAG O ended
32 WORDTAG O must
22 WORDTAG O chance
16 WORDTAG O a.m.
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Thomson
6 WORDTAG O unnamed
4 WORDTAG I-LOC Akron
76 WORDTAG O game
5 WORDTAG O BASKETBALL
7 WORDTAG O liquidity
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Bulgaria
51 WORDTAG O want
17 WORDTAG O qualifier
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Cannes
1 WORDTAG I-PER Colombo
8 WORDTAG O person
38 WORDTAG O previous
5 WORDTAG O badly
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Bochum
13 WORDTAG O thousands
11 WORDTAG O neighbouring
18 WORDTAG O hand
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Wednesday
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Bordeaux
14 WORDTAG O look
9 WORDTAG O representatives
21 WORDTAG O eastern
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Bromwich
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Leon
13 WORDTAG O And
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Miami
9 WORDTAG O resolution
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Two
13 WORDTAG I-ORG Toronto
15 WORDTAG I-ORG LOUIS
10 WORDTAG O Turnover
7 WORDTAG I-PER Luis
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Postal
7 WORDTAG O 15th
91 WORDTAG O reported
10 WORDTAG B-MISC _RARE_
15 WORDTAG O Second
22 WORDTAG O radio
7 WORDTAG O prosecutor
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Oxford
17 WORDTAG O one-day
7 WORDTAG I-ORG ACC
83 WORDTAG O set
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Taiwan
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Winners
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Commercial
3 WORDTAG I-ORG NATIONS
5 WORDTAG I-PER Goran
10 WORDTAG O ran
16 WORDTAG O books
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Helibor
25 WORDTAG O outside
52 WORDTAG O players
6 WORDTAG O involves
6 WORDTAG O mountain
85 WORDTAG O 1996-08-25
2 WORDTAG I-PER )
4 WORDTAG I-LOC GOLF
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Brewers
114 WORDTAG O because
7 WORDTAG I-PER Cedric
33 WORDTAG O 10.
13 WORDTAG I-MISC Nicaraguan
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Amoco
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Germain
4 WORDTAG I-LOC Georgia
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Rapid
6 WORDTAG O supporters
1 WORDTAG I-LOC hospital
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Dublin
47 WORDTAG O television
4 WORDTAG I-MISC :
7 WORDTAG O ask
20 WORDTAG O overall
20 WORDTAG O value
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Cologne
9 WORDTAG O standing
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Bristol
6 WORDTAG I-PER Sandra
2 WORDTAG I-MISC Social
8 WORDTAG I-ORG CVG
2 WORDTAG I-PER May
12 WORDTAG O You
13 WORDTAG I-MISC FRENCH
19 WORDTAG O options
7 WORDTAG O refunds
1 WORDTAG I-PER Cash
1 WORDTAG I-LOC No
46 WORDTAG O later
1 WORDTAG I-MISC India
10 WORDTAG I-PER Colin
21 WORDTAG O ordered
271 WORDTAG O over
14 WORDTAG O +44
6 WORDTAG I-PER Miller
25 WORDTAG O poor
31 WORDTAG O woman
56 WORDTAG O months
7 WORDTAG O attending
12 WORDTAG I-ORG OB
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Newcastle
7 WORDTAG O reveal
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Pirates
5 WORDTAG O boycott
103 WORDTAG O 1996-08-23
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Portsmouth
5 WORDTAG O sectors
11 WORDTAG O takes
3 WORDTAG I-ORG UEFA
24 WORDTAG I-MISC Turkish
7 WORDTAG O street
22 WORDTAG I-LOC Rica
10 WORDTAG O drive
26 WORDTAG O charged
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Kansas
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Lehman
62 WORDTAG O war
5 WORDTAG O walkover
11 WORDTAG O prevent
1 WORDTAG O Winners
7 WORDTAG O 40,000
12 WORDTAG I-PER Washington
6 WORDTAG O seat
1 WORDTAG I-MISC 1992
5 WORDTAG O remarkable
6 WORDTAG O 108
6 WORDTAG O size
6 WORDTAG O northeast
104 WORDTAG I-ORG of
8 WORDTAG O route
28 WORDTAG O see
1 WORDTAG I-ORG bureau
10 WORDTAG O quarter-finals
39 WORDTAG O Standings
7 WORDTAG O grenades
13 WORDTAG O 11th
4 WORDTAG I-LOC DETROIT
13 WORDTAG I-PER Marc
7 WORDTAG O warrants
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Lincoln
8 WORDTAG O scene
15 WORDTAG I-PER Tom
8 WORDTAG O 86
7 WORDTAG O surprise
25 WORDTAG O here
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Auckland
2 WORDTAG O Civil
8 WORDTAG I-PER Lance
5 WORDTAG O excellent
3 WORDTAG O Tennis
6 WORDTAG O respect
12 WORDTAG O quickly
56 WORDTAG O gave
5 WORDTAG I-PER Hatoyama
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Wroclaw
6 WORDTAG O chances
6 WORDTAG O G
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Johannesburg
7 WORDTAG I-PER Habsudova
14 WORDTAG I-LOC COLOMBO
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Ducati
23 WORDTAG O 52
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Singapore
30 WORDTAG O squad
13 WORDTAG O buying
9 WORDTAG O politicians
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Guerrero
15 WORDTAG O RESULT
59 WORDTAG O town
8 WORDTAG I-PER Julie
32 WORDTAG I-LOC Bank
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Rwanda
1 WORDTAG O East
26 WORDTAG O tried
26 WORDTAG I-LOC AMSTERDAM
5 WORDTAG O pending
12 WORDTAG I-LOC Zaire
1 WORDTAG I-LOC W.
7 WORDTAG O Jan
12 WORDTAG O barter
46 WORDTAG O forces
58 WORDTAG O put
10 WORDTAG O row
6 WORDTAG I-PER Karina
13 WORDTAG O claimed
7 WORDTAG O pretty
11 WORDTAG O fishermen
5 WORDTAG O eye
12 WORDTAG O long-term
34 WORDTAG O across
1 WORDTAG B-MISC 2,000
5 WORDTAG O MPs
63 WORDTAG O 7-5
26 WORDTAG I-PER Mullally
1 WORDTAG I-MISC 12th
47 WORDTAG O following
5 WORDTAG O unclear
5 WORDTAG O MONDAY
7 WORDTAG I-PER Date
10 WORDTAG O peso
5 WORDTAG O KV
6 WORDTAG O Dec
16 WORDTAG O Extras
343 WORDTAG O 6
17 WORDTAG O resignation
22 WORDTAG O tabulated
13 WORDTAG O TEST
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Jose
10 WORDTAG O leads
9 WORDTAG O comes
9 WORDTAG O enter
181 WORDTAG O Friday
15 WORDTAG O owned
80 WORDTAG O held
6 WORDTAG O drought
3 WORDTAG I-ORG England
12 WORDTAG O direct
14 WORDTAG O grand
121 WORDTAG O 1996
8 WORDTAG I-MISC Celsius
9 WORDTAG O served
133 WORDTAG O since
11 WORDTAG O Under
5 WORDTAG O painful
5 WORDTAG O commitment
12 WORDTAG I-PER Maria
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Wells
74 WORDTAG O b
107 WORDTAG O third
45 WORDTAG O troops
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Total
2 WORDTAG I-ORG radio
38 WORDTAG I-ORG Co
5 WORDTAG O endorse
5 WORDTAG O Data
17 WORDTAG O operation
1 WORDTAG I-PER Nancy
1 WORDTAG O Grand
124 WORDTAG O officials
34 WORDTAG O stories
53 WORDTAG O dollar
5 WORDTAG O model
4 WORDTAG I-MISC International
5 WORDTAG I-PER Kohl
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Tehran
10 WORDTAG I-PER Oncins
15 WORDTAG I-LOC Brussels
5 WORDTAG I-MISC LAKES
5 WORDTAG O garden
5 WORDTAG I-PER Gianluca
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Zastava
53 WORDTAG O plan
4 WORDTAG I-PER Young
84 WORDTAG O At
7 WORDTAG O occurred
13 WORDTAG O target
31 WORDTAG O hospital
5 WORDTAG O elsewhere
14 WORDTAG O act
8 WORDTAG I-MISC EUROPEAN
7 WORDTAG O benefit
26 WORDTAG O illegal
18 WORDTAG O damage
24 WORDTAG O goal
9 WORDTAG O storm
10 WORDTAG I-PER Mayfair
3 WORDTAG O International
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Valletta
8 WORDTAG I-ORG SEC
35 WORDTAG I-MISC Italian
15 WORDTAG I-ORG Court
68 WORDTAG O seven
6 WORDTAG O phase
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Nigeria
8 WORDTAG O definitely
128 WORDTAG O all
59 WORDTAG O what
15 WORDTAG I-ORG Rotterdam
7 WORDTAG O festival
6 WORDTAG O turnover
16 WORDTAG O medical
7 WORDTAG O normal
22 WORDTAG O cost
6 WORDTAG I-LOC HELSINKI
39 WORDTAG O Police
4 WORDTAG O de
5 WORDTAG I-PER Tauziat
24 WORDTAG I-ORG Association
11 WORDTAG O opposed
40 WORDTAG O 63
13 WORDTAG O information
19 WORDTAG I-PER Sanchez
6 WORDTAG O administrative
5 WORDTAG I-PER Natalya
1 WORDTAG I-MISC La
9 WORDTAG O ready
16 WORDTAG O special
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Guingamp
68 WORDTAG O 25
7 WORDTAG O controls
5 WORDTAG O thrown
16 WORDTAG O basis
31 WORDTAG O brought
17 WORDTAG I-ORG Oakland
7 WORDTAG O flow
7 WORDTAG O .531
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Hyundai
143 WORDTAG O market
10 WORDTAG I-PER Norman
1243 WORDTAG O -
7 WORDTAG O lifting
21 WORDTAG I-LOC Baghdad
28 WORDTAG I-MISC Serb
53 WORDTAG O late
11 WORDTAG O heard
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Commodities
36 WORDTAG I-PER Dutroux
18 WORDTAG I-PER Rubin
10 WORDTAG I-MISC Rwandan
1 WORDTAG I-MISC London
20 WORDTAG I-LOC The
5 WORDTAG O sentences
7 WORDTAG O linking
7 WORDTAG O instead
78 WORDTAG I-MISC British
16 WORDTAG O whole
29 WORDTAG O 0-0
6 WORDTAG O neither
28 WORDTAG O No
7 WORDTAG O specific
17 WORDTAG I-ORG CITY
50 WORDTAG O arrested
7 WORDTAG O WEDNESDAY
30 WORDTAG O likely
23 WORDTAG O 7-4
9 WORDTAG O kills
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Beirut
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Mexican
25 WORDTAG O sell
6 WORDTAG O forcing
12 WORDTAG O dismissed
12 WORDTAG O involving
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Kurdish
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Barnsley
11 WORDTAG O challenge
7 WORDTAG I-MISC A
20 WORDTAG O January
8 WORDTAG I-ORG UNION
11 WORDTAG O operating
5 WORDTAG I-PER Ken
11 WORDTAG O assets
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Western
7 WORDTAG O various
22 WORDTAG O 3-6
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Doncaster
14 WORDTAG O stake
37 WORDTAG I-LOC Canada
7 WORDTAG O identified
5 WORDTAG I-ORG JavaSoft
7 WORDTAG O original
16 WORDTAG I-ORG SEATTLE
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Internet
1 WORDTAG I-MISC 2
1 WORDTAG B-MISC Davis
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Cologne
25 WORDTAG O 'm
4 WORDTAG I-LOC Florence
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Ramallah
22 WORDTAG I-PER Johnson
8 WORDTAG O Date
13 WORDTAG I-ORG Barcelona
46 WORDTAG O southern
7 WORDTAG I-PER Anne
13 WORDTAG O dangerous
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Team
13 WORDTAG O limited
59 WORDTAG O military
1 WORDTAG I-PER Toronto
6 WORDTAG I-MISC COUNTY
8 WORDTAG I-LOC Bridge
48 WORDTAG I-MISC DIVISION
12 WORDTAG O debut
8 WORDTAG I-PER Francisco
4 WORDTAG O Series
30 WORDTAG O estimated
10 WORDTAG O necessary
23 WORDTAG O firm
11 WORDTAG I-PER Hashimoto
1 WORDTAG I-LOC 31
12 WORDTAG O immediate
5 WORDTAG I-PER Raichev
19 WORDTAG O sides
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Venezuela
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Bistrita
7 WORDTAG O restaurant
2 WORDTAG I-MISC North
6 WORDTAG O maker
15 WORDTAG I-ORG ANGELES
6 WORDTAG O SER
5 WORDTAG I-ORG NBH
11 WORDTAG O tough
259 WORDTAG O 7
24 WORDTAG O 77
3 WORDTAG I-MISC Civil
4 WORDTAG I-PER Kan
10 WORDTAG O owns
24 WORDTAG O bond
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Bratislava
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Government
1 WORDTAG O Black
6 WORDTAG O Dividend
29 WORDTAG I-ORG SAN
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Colombia
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Startup
13 WORDTAG O ransom
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Kansas
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Islamic
5 WORDTAG O container
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Soccer
8 WORDTAG O prompt
5 WORDTAG I-PER Sosa
12 WORDTAG O Sales
27 WORDTAG O scheduled
1 WORDTAG I-MISC program
6 WORDTAG O 145
9 WORDTAG I-PER Salisbury
5 WORDTAG O sending
25 WORDTAG O civil
6 WORDTAG O majors
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Chesterfield
7 WORDTAG O age
17 WORDTAG O losing
9 WORDTAG I-ORG MFS
7 WORDTAG I-PER Rosset
57 WORDTAG O goals
5 WORDTAG O legs
5 WORDTAG O assistant
33 WORDTAG O 54
4 WORDTAG I-MISC Conference
167 WORDTAG O 9
5 WORDTAG O crowds
5 WORDTAG O Fax
11 WORDTAG O promised
40 WORDTAG O past
19 WORDTAG O For
5 WORDTAG O fours
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Dacom
11 WORDTAG O residents
5 WORDTAG O BY
9 WORDTAG O demanded
9 WORDTAG O reasons
2 WORDTAG I-PER Le
6 WORDTAG O faster
6 WORDTAG O franc
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Krakow
38 WORDTAG I-LOC Lanka
8 WORDTAG O proposals
6 WORDTAG I-ORG MSV
10 WORDTAG O All
23 WORDTAG O compared
15 WORDTAG O driver
6 WORDTAG O rainfall
67 WORDTAG O minute
56 WORDTAG O behind
5 WORDTAG I-PER Herbert
8 WORDTAG I-PER Gilbert
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Anyang
6 WORDTAG O highway
6 WORDTAG O climbed
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Nijmegen
5 WORDTAG O offering
86 WORDTAG O June
20 WORDTAG I-MISC CUP
59 WORDTAG O both
8 WORDTAG O threat
6 WORDTAG O kilometre
13 WORDTAG O picked
62 WORDTAG O go
5 WORDTAG O provided
24 WORDTAG O director
8 WORDTAG O serving
8 WORDTAG O king
13 WORDTAG O wins
5 WORDTAG I-PER Wells
24 WORDTAG O penalty
9 WORDTAG I-PER Smicer
16 WORDTAG O things
29 WORDTAG I-LOC Poland
25 WORDTAG O wheat
5 WORDTAG O A-rated
5 WORDTAG O warning
14 WORDTAG I-MISC Jewish
2 WORDTAG I-MISC Exchange
13 WORDTAG O religious
6 WORDTAG O civilians
6 WORDTAG O experience
7 WORDTAG I-MISC West
27 WORDTAG O times
61 WORDTAG I-ORG Inc
16 WORDTAG I-ORG Tigers
36 WORDTAG O conference
17 WORDTAG O church
2 WORDTAG I-LOC State
5 WORDTAG O sports
37 WORDTAG O future
14 WORDTAG O 3-1
2 WORDTAG I-ORG War
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Headingley
7 WORDTAG O foreigners
5 WORDTAG O 1948
4 WORDTAG I-ORG World
7 WORDTAG I-ORG SBC
6 WORDTAG O kidnappers
102 WORDTAG O them
22 WORDTAG O Some
76 WORDTAG O took
20 WORDTAG I-MISC National
5 WORDTAG O walking
7 WORDTAG O Most
1 WORDTAG I-ORG am
9 WORDTAG I-PER Davies
11 WORDTAG I-ORG British
13 WORDTAG I-LOC Afghanistan
11 WORDTAG O previously
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Lincoln
7 WORDTAG O 109
1 WORDTAG I-MISC My
7 WORDTAG I-LOC ATLANTA
5 WORDTAG I-LOC JYVASKYLA
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Southampton
5 WORDTAG O deny
11 WORDTAG O towns
20 WORDTAG O mission
15 WORDTAG O fight
8 WORDTAG I-PER Aslan
8 WORDTAG O medal
553 WORDTAG O it
22 WORDTAG O western
11 WORDTAG O lei
7 WORDTAG O PM
37 WORDTAG O without
14 WORDTAG I-ORG Leeds
2 WORDTAG I-MISC Financial
8 WORDTAG O Gov
5 WORDTAG I-PER Karol
14 WORDTAG O announcement
19 WORDTAG O risk
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Swedish
23 WORDTAG O similar
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Vienna
41 WORDTAG O index
8 WORDTAG O elect
5 WORDTAG O sexual
8 WORDTAG O link
7 WORDTAG O assessment
6 WORDTAG I-PER Sharif
14 WORDTAG O V
4 WORDTAG I-LOC ST
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Company
8 WORDTAG O names
1 WORDTAG I-ORG democracy
10 WORDTAG O billions
6 WORDTAG O impossible
5 WORDTAG O independent
306 WORDTAG O they
19 WORDTAG O orders
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Conference
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Industry
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Insurance
2 WORDTAG I-ORG magazine
7 WORDTAG O ca
25 WORDTAG O conditions
581 WORDTAG O 4
57 WORDTAG I-LOC Czech
1 WORDTAG I-MISC II
3 WORDTAG I-LOC FLORIDA
11 WORDTAG O attend
1 WORDTAG I-PER Post
57 WORDTAG O make
13 WORDTAG I-PER Thorpe
5 WORDTAG O escaped
11 WORDTAG O determine
5 WORDTAG O word
7 WORDTAG O fallen
5 WORDTAG I-LOC LANKA
81 WORDTAG I-LOC Sweden
6 WORDTAG O placings
16 WORDTAG O losses
7 WORDTAG O popular
8 WORDTAG O mandate
5 WORDTAG O owners
21 WORDTAG O black
6 WORDTAG O manufacturers
7 WORDTAG O choice
4 WORDTAG O School
19 WORDTAG I-PER Chris
122 WORDTAG O there
71 WORDTAG O 100
43 WORDTAG O share
11 WORDTAG O spent
37 WORDTAG O available
25 WORDTAG O 1-1
24 WORDTAG O denotes
4 WORDTAG I-PER Games
19243 WORDTAG O _RARE_
5 WORDTAG O iron
7 WORDTAG O true
5 WORDTAG I-PER Amanda
8 WORDTAG O century
34 WORDTAG O 59
8 WORDTAG O organised
362 WORDTAG O $
16 WORDTAG I-MISC Major
8 WORDTAG I-PER Marco
5 WORDTAG I-PER Kafelnikov
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Colchester
5 WORDTAG I-PER Naoko
19 WORDTAG O farmers
5 WORDTAG O youth
18 WORDTAG O paid
2 WORDTAG O Council
5 WORDTAG I-MISC McLaren
330 WORDTAG O would
20 WORDTAG O GB
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Arch
3 WORDTAG O Centre
9 WORDTAG I-MISC Toyota
5 WORDTAG O merely
14 WORDTAG O C
11 WORDTAG O first-half
6 WORDTAG O Also
66 WORDTAG O left
11 WORDTAG O above
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Karachi
6 WORDTAG O Maybe
15 WORDTAG O figure
7 WORDTAG O stadium
9 WORDTAG O nor
37 WORDTAG O ministry
10 WORDTAG O carry
6 WORDTAG I-PER Ballanger
4 WORDTAG I-MISC Hutu
6 WORDTAG O loaded
6 WORDTAG O slight
13 WORDTAG O cuts
6 WORDTAG O midday
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Stoke
2 WORDTAG O SERIES
16 WORDTAG O community
53 WORDTAG O price
17 WORDTAG O survey
28 WORDTAG O 76
5 WORDTAG I-PER Brandes
5 WORDTAG I-PER Patricia
6 WORDTAG O blame
22 WORDTAG O far
5 WORDTAG O baby
48 WORDTAG I-MISC World
9 WORDTAG O commanding
6 WORDTAG O leftist
19 WORDTAG O sets
22 WORDTAG O province
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Karachi
28 WORDTAG I-PER Waqar
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Federation
1 WORDTAG O RUGBY
17 WORDTAG I-ORG BALTIMORE
6 WORDTAG I-MISC WORLD
5 WORDTAG O Among
2 WORDTAG I-PER Law
5 WORDTAG I-MISC NETHERLANDS
8 WORDTAG O grade
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Akron
5 WORDTAG O restored
8 WORDTAG O headed
5 WORDTAG O destitute
7 WORDTAG O propaganda
121 WORDTAG O Minister
16 WORDTAG O states
10 WORDTAG O investigating
8 WORDTAG I-MISC Names
106 WORDTAG O did
53 WORDTAG O get
4 WORDTAG I-ORG MOODY
18 WORDTAG O voting
7 WORDTAG O N
11 WORDTAG O training
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Gazprom
40 WORDTAG O current
167 WORDTAG O 1996-08-28
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Colombo
1 WORDTAG I-MISC ,
17 WORDTAG I-PER Stich
10 WORDTAG I-PER Lee
6 WORDTAG I-ORG EPR
5 WORDTAG O import
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Switzerland
28 WORDTAG O exports
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Cardinals
11 WORDTAG O born
309 WORDTAG I-LOC U.S.
20 WORDTAG I-PER Jose
7 WORDTAG O politics
11 WORDTAG O subject
2 WORDTAG I-PER Price
5 WORDTAG O detective
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Systems
1 WORDTAG I-MISC USA
6 WORDTAG O m
23 WORDTAG I-MISC Sudanese
9 WORDTAG O 9373-1800
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Iran
15 WORDTAG I-ORG State
50 WORDTAG O economic
52 WORDTAG O agency
10 WORDTAG O appointed
6 WORDTAG O dragged
7 WORDTAG O 521-8
18 WORDTAG I-LOC Denmark
11 WORDTAG I-PER Hill
7 WORDTAG O bullish
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Saudi
7 WORDTAG I-PER Jean
14 WORDTAG O streak
5 WORDTAG O asking
13 WORDTAG O sanctions
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Oxford
9 WORDTAG O registrations
13 WORDTAG O book
5 WORDTAG O batsman
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Cubs
8 WORDTAG I-PER Lloyd
19 WORDTAG O caught
6 WORDTAG I-PER Fleurian
105 WORDTAG O win
35 WORDTAG O disease
214 WORDTAG O also
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Chemlon
7 WORDTAG I-PER Terry
6 WORDTAG I-MISC UEFA
1 WORDTAG O SUPER
16 WORDTAG O building
25 WORDTAG O letter
5 WORDTAG I-PER Pinas
16 WORDTAG I-PER William
10 WORDTAG I-LOC Colorado
5 WORDTAG I-LOC BUENOS
10 WORDTAG O beef
9 WORDTAG O base
13 WORDTAG I-ORG University
5 WORDTAG O imported
12 WORDTAG O allegations
10 WORDTAG O potential
5 WORDTAG O trend
5 WORDTAG I-ORG interior
5 WORDTAG O Add
48 WORDTAG O including
33 WORDTAG O press
2 WORDTAG O serie
767 WORDTAG O that
2 WORDTAG I-LOC free
5 WORDTAG O Chief
8 WORDTAG I-PER Perry
27 WORDTAG O title
9 WORDTAG O dozen
5 WORDTAG O push
20 WORDTAG I-PER Medvedev
13 WORDTAG O mad
9 WORDTAG O document
5 WORDTAG O recorded
8 WORDTAG O favour
125 WORDTAG O 1996-08-22
63 WORDTAG O 24
7 WORDTAG O settled
21 WORDTAG I-MISC Indian
6 WORDTAG I-MISC Convention
5 WORDTAG O payments
21 WORDTAG I-LOC SAN
6 WORDTAG O ranking
1 WORDTAG I-LOC People
17 WORDTAG O spot
20 WORDTAG I-MISC of
7 WORDTAG I-PER Weld
5 WORDTAG O advice
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Trade
439 WORDTAG O who
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Black
14 WORDTAG O though
1496 WORDTAG O 's
6 WORDTAG O 1980s
13 WORDTAG O four-day
16 WORDTAG I-ORG Atletico
6 WORDTAG I-MISC Frenchman
5 WORDTAG O roads
6 WORDTAG I-PER Chelsea
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Telekom
216 WORDTAG O second
46 WORDTAG O DIVISION
5 WORDTAG O style
4 WORDTAG O Four
9 WORDTAG O prepared
5 WORDTAG O placed
1846 WORDTAG O said
5 WORDTAG O effects
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Birmingham
24 WORDTAG O system
7 WORDTAG O smaller
9 WORDTAG O especially
23 WORDTAG I-PER Steve
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Treasury
5 WORDTAG O 1.2
1 WORDTAG I-LOC School
21 WORDTAG O open
16 WORDTAG I-PER Martinez
1 WORDTAG I-ORG 2000
18 WORDTAG O move
48 WORDTAG O office
13 WORDTAG I-ORG Schalke
10 WORDTAG I-PER Jan
3 WORDTAG I-MISC SUPER
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Capital
10 WORDTAG O project
17 WORDTAG I-PER Russell
6 WORDTAG O Shr
5 WORDTAG I-PER Andreas
5 WORDTAG O 852
77 WORDTAG O elections
18 WORDTAG O key
54 WORDTAG O Women
30 WORDTAG O passengers
14 WORDTAG I-MISC Afghan
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Arkansas
6 WORDTAG O kms
9 WORDTAG O established
10 WORDTAG O flights
15 WORDTAG O followed
67 WORDTAG I-LOC YORK
22 WORDTAG I-PER Sohail
9 WORDTAG O permission
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Park
24 WORDTAG O break
5 WORDTAG O bowled
6 WORDTAG O global
55 WORDTAG O FIRST
11 WORDTAG O improved
15 WORDTAG O wounded
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Red
6 WORDTAG I-LOC BAGHDAD
26 WORDTAG O met
6 WORDTAG O Soccer
15 WORDTAG I-ORG PHILADELPHIA
6 WORDTAG I-PER Giles
6 WORDTAG I-PER Mubarak
26 WORDTAG O know
5 WORDTAG O 1-106
12 WORDTAG O funds
46 WORDTAG O may
10 WORDTAG O generally
7 WORDTAG O revenues
5 WORDTAG O communications
18 WORDTAG O 81
7 WORDTAG O discussions
11 WORDTAG I-PER Simon
16 WORDTAG I-PER Stewart
16 WORDTAG O biggest
108 WORDTAG O home
28 WORDTAG I-LOC Taiwan
8 WORDTAG O records
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Chorzow
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Leicester
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Poland
5 WORDTAG O filled
15 WORDTAG O looking
7 WORDTAG O .02
75 WORDTAG O lead
14 WORDTAG O rupiah
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Japan
9 WORDTAG O shipments
46 WORDTAG O men
25 WORDTAG I-PER Khan
10 WORDTAG O clearly
45 WORDTAG O reporters
11 WORDTAG O friendly
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Latvia
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Aires
5 WORDTAG O referendum
16 WORDTAG O feel
73 WORDTAG O results
18 WORDTAG I-MISC Wimbledon
13 WORDTAG I-ORG Gencor
60 WORDTAG O called
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Dhaka
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Georgia
13 WORDTAG O wants
7 WORDTAG O dark
6 WORDTAG O 7.0
7 WORDTAG O hopes
9 WORDTAG O meetings
4 WORDTAG I-LOC Belgrade
5 WORDTAG O boats
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Buenos
9 WORDTAG I-PER Haga
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Colchester
7 WORDTAG O formally
7 WORDTAG O holders
20 WORDTAG I-ORG Council
1 WORDTAG I-LOC north
3 WORDTAG O Spring
212 WORDTAG O Tuesday
24 WORDTAG O village
5 WORDTAG O seems
59 WORDTAG O prices
52 WORDTAG I-ORG St
131 WORDTAG O '
79 WORDTAG I-ORG Reuters
5 WORDTAG O 4.4
40 WORDTAG O business
8 WORDTAG O tension
7 WORDTAG O flown
9 WORDTAG O H1
37 WORDTAG I-LOC Zealand
17 WORDTAG O 1-6
9 WORDTAG O travelling
6 WORDTAG O disarmament
9 WORDTAG I-PER Enqvist
16 WORDTAG I-ORG Congress
55 WORDTAG O opposition
6 WORDTAG I-PER Kevin
349 WORDTAG O two
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Algiers
15 WORDTAG O moment
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Australia
1 WORDTAG I-PER of
6 WORDTAG O PRICE
57 WORDTAG O trade
164 WORDTAG O no
15 WORDTAG O pact
14 WORDTAG O snapped
14 WORDTAG O almost
42 WORDTAG O countries
11 WORDTAG I-PER James
1 WORDTAG I-MISC CHICAGO
85 WORDTAG O 71
11 WORDTAG I-LOC SYDNEY
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Canada
17 WORDTAG I-PER van
27 WORDTAG O border
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Lynch
5 WORDTAG I-PER Bernd
12 WORDTAG I-ORG Benetton
7 WORDTAG O troubled
7 WORDTAG O signs
11 WORDTAG O send
4 WORDTAG I-ORG 'S
12 WORDTAG I-ORG Louis
13 WORDTAG I-MISC Tour
5 WORDTAG I-LOC FRANKFURT
23 WORDTAG O land
2 WORDTAG O Public
19 WORDTAG O Sept
5 WORDTAG O venue
9 WORDTAG O corporate
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Eritrea
12 WORDTAG I-ORG Inc.
1 WORDTAG I-PER II
14 WORDTAG O anything
5 WORDTAG O demands
5 WORDTAG O violation
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Sun
15 WORDTAG O commander
12 WORDTAG I-PER Huber
8 WORDTAG O treatment
8 WORDTAG I-LOC BOSTON
8 WORDTAG O 12.0
83 WORDTAG O talks
26 WORDTAG I-MISC OPEN
15 WORDTAG I-PER S.
13 WORDTAG O stages
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Bangladesh
8 WORDTAG I-MISC Americans
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Libya
10 WORDTAG O guilty
17 WORDTAG O drove
16 WORDTAG O job
1 WORDTAG I-ORG division
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Democrat
5 WORDTAG I-MISC East
5 WORDTAG O trafficking
5 WORDTAG O penalties
10 WORDTAG O serve
13 WORDTAG O hands
1 WORDTAG I-ORG JERUSALEM
557 WORDTAG O has
21 WORDTAG I-ORG Security
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Kan
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Community
17 WORDTAG O although
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Munich
20 WORDTAG I-PER N.
9 WORDTAG I-ORG County
11 WORDTAG I-ORG )
15 WORDTAG O presence
10 WORDTAG I-PER Bailey
34 WORDTAG O October
10 WORDTAG O growing
18 WORDTAG I-MISC Serbs
6 WORDTAG O 1986
10 WORDTAG O study
5 WORDTAG O collision
36 WORDTAG I-LOC Ireland
7 WORDTAG O quality
11 WORDTAG O material
3 WORDTAG I-PER Sheffield
5 WORDTAG I-PER Grobbelaar
7 WORDTAG O deposit
6 WORDTAG I-PER Dean
2 WORDTAG O Team
43 WORDTAG O test
8 WORDTAG I-ORG GKS
15 WORDTAG O houses
19 WORDTAG O 4-6
6 WORDTAG I-MISC Index
6 WORDTAG O 26th
33 WORDTAG O Two
10 WORDTAG O lending
16 WORDTAG O running
11 WORDTAG I-MISC Scottish
8 WORDTAG I-PER Miguel
4 WORDTAG I-LOC Federation
36 WORDTAG O case
7 WORDTAG I-LOC SEATTLE
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Southern
8 WORDTAG O rallied
9 WORDTAG O 1989
8 WORDTAG O extremely
24 WORDTAG O winner
16 WORDTAG O caused
12 WORDTAG O 212
4 WORDTAG I-LOC British
7 WORDTAG O factors
21 WORDTAG I-MISC C$
2 WORDTAG I-PER Paulo
5 WORDTAG I-MISC CLASSIC
11 WORDTAG O judge
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Budapest
9 WORDTAG O trillion
8 WORDTAG I-PER Andy
14 WORDTAG O boat
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Massachusetts
23 WORDTAG O %
6 WORDTAG O Current
6 WORDTAG O decline
85 WORDTAG O added
6 WORDTAG I-ORG America
9 WORDTAG O expectations
7 WORDTAG O pledged
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Home
89 WORDTAG O team
2 WORDTAG I-MISC One
20 WORDTAG O AND
12 WORDTAG I-PER Waugh
74 WORDTAG O due
5 WORDTAG O taxi
6 WORDTAG I-MISC 96
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Bureau
6 WORDTAG O 3-2
3 WORDTAG I-ORG '
38 WORDTAG I-MISC U.S.
5 WORDTAG O normally
11 WORDTAG O university
945 WORDTAG O 0
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Wellman
10 WORDTAG I-PER Benjamin
7 WORDTAG O moving
25 WORDTAG I-MISC Chinese
13 WORDTAG I-LOC Greece
12 WORDTAG O every
6 WORDTAG O receive
1 WORDTAG I-ORG No
66 WORDTAG O says
6 WORDTAG O birds
14 WORDTAG I-PER Boris
6 WORDTAG O option
8 WORDTAG O monthly
207 WORDTAG O It
12 WORDTAG I-LOC JOHANNESBURG
17 WORDTAG O telephone
17 WORDTAG O port
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Reform
14 WORDTAG I-ORG MILWAUKEE
20 WORDTAG O 1990
7 WORDTAG O lbw
12 WORDTAG O 78
6 WORDTAG I-PER Stephanie
13 WORDTAG O 2-2
7 WORDTAG O language
5 WORDTAG I-PER Pol
6 WORDTAG I-PER Rocca
19 WORDTAG O midfielder
21 WORDTAG O guilders
36 WORDTAG O help
8 WORDTAG O Rating
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Bayer
2 WORDTAG I-PER Power
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Nasdaq
15 WORDTAG I-PER Gore
21 WORDTAG I-PER Teresa
13 WORDTAG O delivery
6 WORDTAG O factor
11 WORDTAG O organisers
11 WORDTAG O posted
74 WORDTAG O saying
59 WORDTAG O ago
21 WORDTAG O traders
33 WORDTAG O strong
11 WORDTAG I-PER Adrian
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Rabobank
13 WORDTAG I-ORG Pauli
6 WORDTAG O LATEST
1 WORDTAG O Index
7 WORDTAG O rains
7 WORDTAG O cent
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Barcelona
5 WORDTAG I-PER Yihye
157 WORDTAG O some
11 WORDTAG O table
25 WORDTAG O opened
5 WORDTAG O matter
6 WORDTAG I-LOC LISBON
28 WORDTAG O holiday
31 WORDTAG O guerrillas
44 WORDTAG O general
24 WORDTAG O needed
23 WORDTAG O W
21 WORDTAG O 400
24 WORDTAG O flight
11 WORDTAG I-MISC Slam
38 WORDTAG O 62
8 WORDTAG O fob
12 WORDTAG I-ORG Medical
32 WORDTAG O markets
5 WORDTAG O 2.6
6 WORDTAG O DRAW
5 WORDTAG I-PER Barry
7 WORDTAG I-PER Popov
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Municipal
124 WORDTAG O 1996-08-29
21 WORDTAG I-ORG Department
34 WORDTAG I-PER Wasim
11 WORDTAG I-PER Atherton
15 WORDTAG I-ORG West
67 WORDTAG O our
10 WORDTAG O WITH
159 WORDTAG O under
22 WORDTAG O nation
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Portugal
35 WORDTAG O embassy
10 WORDTAG O extra
13 WORDTAG I-PER Malik
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Royal
5 WORDTAG I-LOC LOS
9 WORDTAG I-PER Sarah
3 WORDTAG I-PER Stadler
16 WORDTAG O media
9 WORDTAG O Following
14 WORDTAG I-LOC Syria
29 WORDTAG O workers
1 WORDTAG O Community
15 WORDTAG O ruled
106 WORDTAG O spokesman
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Oklahoma
5 WORDTAG O commentary
8 WORDTAG I-MISC HK$
12 WORDTAG O defending
6 WORDTAG O deposed
5 WORDTAG O changing
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Brooks
8 WORDTAG O Eight
108 WORDTAG O she
7 WORDTAG O improvement
7 WORDTAG O Of
11 WORDTAG O request
9 WORDTAG O receiving
17 WORDTAG O once
7 WORDTAG O humanitarian
5 WORDTAG I-LOC N.J.
8 WORDTAG O 54th
38 WORDTAG O winning
16 WORDTAG O SCHEDULE
4 WORDTAG I-LOC Northampton
5 WORDTAG O containing
9 WORDTAG O .496
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Kiev
17 WORDTAG O blamed
1 WORDTAG I-PER Spring
2846 WORDTAG O (
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Convention
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Subaru
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Zenith
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Nice
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Tottenham
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Interpol
5 WORDTAG O edition
50 WORDTAG O chief
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Ecuador
7 WORDTAG O addressed
5 WORDTAG O racing
10 WORDTAG O operations
124 WORDTAG I-LOC England
14 WORDTAG I-ORG for
23 WORDTAG O broke
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Reef
5 WORDTAG I-ORG PSG
5 WORDTAG O intercepted
5 WORDTAG O recalled
5 WORDTAG O directly
7 WORDTAG I-PER Mitchell
7 WORDTAG I-LOC WARSAW
5 WORDTAG I-LOC DHAKA
6 WORDTAG O UP
5 WORDTAG I-PER Strang
5 WORDTAG I-LOC DUBAI
10 WORDTAG O Other
6 WORDTAG O accuses
8 WORDTAG O AUG
5 WORDTAG O climb
44 WORDTAG O ...
12 WORDTAG I-ORG Yamaha
5 WORDTAG O loans
26 WORDTAG O 'S
2 WORDTAG I-PER Villa
19 WORDTAG O overnight
18 WORDTAG O positive
6 WORDTAG I-PER Fischler
5 WORDTAG O boxcar
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Spartak
16 WORDTAG I-LOC Burundi
20 WORDTAG O domestic
6 WORDTAG O replacement
8 WORDTAG O conducted
5 WORDTAG O platform
4 WORDTAG I-ORG George
6 WORDTAG O fighters
7 WORDTAG I-LOC KANSAS
9 WORDTAG O About
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Front
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Bielefeld
7 WORDTAG I-PER Barbara
13 WORDTAG O handed
7 WORDTAG O weight
6 WORDTAG O split
5 WORDTAG I-PER Silva
6 WORDTAG O ....
71 WORDTAG I-MISC Open
44 WORDTAG O 1994
7 WORDTAG I-PER Pioline
81 WORDTAG O now
13 WORDTAG O fired
10 WORDTAG O fraud
5 WORDTAG O raising
5 WORDTAG O winds
12 WORDTAG O opinion
5 WORDTAG I-LOC AIRES
5 WORDTAG O ranked
5 WORDTAG O engine
17 WORDTAG I-PER Anwar
4 WORDTAG I-MISC Mitsubishi
26 WORDTAG O comment
19 WORDTAG O 90
5 WORDTAG O friends
9 WORDTAG O stopped
28 WORDTAG O sold
10 WORDTAG O epidemic
15 WORDTAG I-LOC TOKYO
20 WORDTAG O 200
5 WORDTAG O pipes
15 WORDTAG O slightly
4 WORDTAG I-LOC USA
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Brazil
6 WORDTAG O 5-1
20 WORDTAG O union
117 WORDTAG O 6-4
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Coast
19 WORDTAG O wanted
12 WORDTAG O site
25 WORDTAG O percentage
29 WORDTAG O better
10 WORDTAG O certain
7 WORDTAG O 83
12 WORDTAG I-ORG PKK
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Basque
5 WORDTAG I-PER Larry
9 WORDTAG O republic
36 WORDTAG O tour
25 WORDTAG O change
6 WORDTAG O 58th
28 WORDTAG O earnings
3617 WORDTAG O of
28 WORDTAG I-MISC Japanese
13 WORDTAG I-PER Banharn
6 WORDTAG O technical
37 WORDTAG O cash
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Leicestershire
37 WORDTAG I-PER Akram
1 WORDTAG O League
8 WORDTAG O systems
25 WORDTAG O even
20 WORDTAG I-LOC PAKISTAN
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Liu
15 WORDTAG O futures
6 WORDTAG O consensus
13 WORDTAG O helped
1 WORDTAG I-PER Virginia
19 WORDTAG O analyst
5 WORDTAG O .527
155 WORDTAG O But
30 WORDTAG O call
5 WORDTAG O association
6 WORDTAG O briefly
9 WORDTAG O People
7 WORDTAG O class
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Centre
9 WORDTAG O holding
5 WORDTAG O fined
25 WORDTAG O tie
7 WORDTAG O 11.
6 WORDTAG I-PER Linford
8 WORDTAG I-PER Svetlana
10 WORDTAG O why
19 WORDTAG I-LOC WASHINGTON
5 WORDTAG O diverted
1 WORDTAG I-MISC First
10 WORDTAG I-PER Tendulkar
5 WORDTAG O medals
4 WORDTAG I-ORG OFFICIAL
30 WORDTAG O companies
6 WORDTAG O quit
29 WORDTAG O named
7362 WORDTAG O .
78 WORDTAG O around
31 WORDTAG O come
5 WORDTAG I-LOC ZIMBABWE
2 WORDTAG I-MISC Four
7 WORDTAG O river
37 WORDTAG O led
26 WORDTAG O struck
11 WORDTAG O fast
27 WORDTAG I-LOC East
12 WORDTAG O democracy
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Philadelphia
12 WORDTAG I-LOC Khartoum
6 WORDTAG O slaughter
19 WORDTAG O charge
197 WORDTAG O 10
15 WORDTAG O light
1 WORDTAG I-ORG vehicles
19 WORDTAG O competition
5 WORDTAG O Sir
9 WORDTAG O capped
5 WORDTAG I-PER Jorge
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Larnaca
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Columbia
5 WORDTAG O shift
5 WORDTAG O quake
7 WORDTAG I-LOC CAIRO
6 WORDTAG O irregularities
34 WORDTAG O service
6 WORDTAG O dealing
27 WORDTAG O straight
14 WORDTAG O rally
5 WORDTAG O acquire
17 WORDTAG O concern
12 WORDTAG O front
10 WORDTAG O announce
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Zurich
9 WORDTAG O present
5 WORDTAG I-LOC UAE
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Puchon
10 WORDTAG O create
9 WORDTAG O researchers
16 WORDTAG I-LOC Gaza
71 WORDTAG O final
12 WORDTAG O afternoon
12 WORDTAG O millions
6 WORDTAG I-PER Yassin
5 WORDTAG O riyal
45 WORDTAG O way
23 WORDTAG O trial
16 WORDTAG I-MISC Slovak
5 WORDTAG O defends
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Betaseron
7 WORDTAG I-PER Jack
5 WORDTAG O Opposition
5 WORDTAG I-PER Joyce
6 WORDTAG I-PER Costantino
7 WORDTAG I-PER Weaver
6 WORDTAG O 80th
8 WORDTAG I-PER Kelly
9 WORDTAG O GOLF
6 WORDTAG O medallist
582 WORDTAG O he
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Barbara
24 WORDTAG O PRESS
6 WORDTAG I-PER Rabbani
8 WORDTAG O unknown
6 WORDTAG O toward
7 WORDTAG I-ORG JC
12 WORDTAG I-MISC '
8 WORDTAG I-PER Lanusse
37 WORDTAG O vote
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Pittsburgh
31 WORDTAG O TENNIS
6 WORDTAG I-ORG AOL
8 WORDTAG O schedule
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Atlanta
14 WORDTAG I-PER Alan
43 WORDTAG I-LOC Brazil
8 WORDTAG O decree
10 WORDTAG O calls
7 WORDTAG O controlled
7 WORDTAG O activists
17 WORDTAG I-ORG Munich
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Community
1 WORDTAG I-PER the
5 WORDTAG O audience
7 WORDTAG O 90th
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Jordanian
1466 WORDTAG I-LOC _RARE_
10 WORDTAG I-LOC Jakarta
6 WORDTAG O provinces
6 WORDTAG I-PER Ross
12 WORDTAG I-LOC White
10 WORDTAG O wrote
6 WORDTAG I-PER McEwen
7275 WORDTAG O ,
5 WORDTAG I-PER Necmettin
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Porto
8 WORDTAG O initially
8 WORDTAG O Several
16 WORDTAG O forward
5 WORDTAG O freight
7 WORDTAG I-PER MaliVai
5 WORDTAG I-PER Tommy
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Togo
7 WORDTAG O sharp
5462 WORDTAG I-PER _RARE_
10 WORDTAG O loan
6 WORDTAG I-PER Whittall
10 WORDTAG O OUT
8 WORDTAG O plus
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Palestinian
16 WORDTAG O situation
20 WORDTAG O 542
9 WORDTAG O solution
19 WORDTAG I-PER Aamir
5 WORDTAG O missionary
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Sittard
22 WORDTAG I-ORG NATO
121 WORDTAG O 1996-08-27
6 WORDTAG I-PER Moura
27 WORDTAG I-LOC Washington
14 WORDTAG I-PER Jones
8 WORDTAG O DIV
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Human
20 WORDTAG O stay
7 WORDTAG O quarterly
9 WORDTAG O 1.5
19 WORDTAG O teams
9 WORDTAG O successful
5 WORDTAG O riding
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Second
7 WORDTAG O closes
33 WORDTAG O April
18 WORDTAG O child
8 WORDTAG I-LOC Central
6 WORDTAG O 3.5
33 WORDTAG O BASEBALL
7 WORDTAG O regime
6 WORDTAG O widespread
9 WORDTAG O council
7 WORDTAG O claims
5 WORDTAG O 941
25 WORDTAG O course
35 WORDTAG O cut
7 WORDTAG O firing
10 WORDTAG O cars
43 WORDTAG O decision
7 WORDTAG O disappointed
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Kabul
22 WORDTAG O volume
8 WORDTAG I-LOC Yemen
8 WORDTAG O negative
17 WORDTAG O BEAT
7 WORDTAG O happen
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Sofia
60 WORDTAG O meet
14 WORDTAG O CYCLING
10 WORDTAG I-ORG NEC
22 WORDTAG I-MISC Iranian
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Auckland
7 WORDTAG O bread
6 WORDTAG I-MISC Miss
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Lewis
7 WORDTAG O active
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Polonia
5 WORDTAG O factory
14 WORDTAG O kph
29 WORDTAG O use
12 WORDTAG I-PER Asif
12 WORDTAG O offices
14 WORDTAG O 6.0
26 WORDTAG O nuclear
5 WORDTAG I-PER Els
7 WORDTAG I-ORG St.
8 WORDTAG O voted
5 WORDTAG O rated
8 WORDTAG O revenue
5 WORDTAG I-ORG East
8 WORDTAG O winter
14 WORDTAG O banned
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Blackburn
5 WORDTAG O replaced
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Kong
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Duisburg
8 WORDTAG O violent
5 WORDTAG O preferred
2 WORDTAG I-PER Ruch
7 WORDTAG I-PER Simpson
17 WORDTAG O cabinet
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Promodes
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Caen
1 WORDTAG I-MISC The
37 WORDTAG O plane
1 WORDTAG I-LOC El
5 WORDTAG I-PER Lopez
4 WORDTAG O ISS
11 WORDTAG O appear
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Havre
5 WORDTAG I-LOC JOSE
13 WORDTAG I-ORG Yankees
11 WORDTAG O faces
5 WORDTAG O whales
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Rally
23 WORDTAG O 1991
71 WORDTAG I-LOC Belgium
7 WORDTAG O explosives
47 WORDTAG I-PER Yeltsin
6 WORDTAG I-MISC KOREAN
106 WORDTAG O expected
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Elect
20 WORDTAG O ethnic
12 WORDTAG O thing
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Tass
8 WORDTAG O idea
6 WORDTAG O 14.
3 WORDTAG O Ten
15 WORDTAG O shooting
6 WORDTAG O Affairs
155 WORDTAG O 8
14 WORDTAG O abroad
22 WORDTAG O unit
31 WORDTAG O charges
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Lodz
6 WORDTAG I-PER Erbakan
8 WORDTAG I-ORG in
5 WORDTAG O noon
7 WORDTAG O knee
5 WORDTAG I-ORG ministry
22 WORDTAG I-LOC Indonesia
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Freiburg
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Indian
13 WORDTAG O lines
6 WORDTAG O affair
10 WORDTAG I-PER Raymond
8 WORDTAG I-MISC Croatian
8 WORDTAG O Six
7 WORDTAG O allocated
6 WORDTAG I-ORG ING
13 WORDTAG I-LOC America
6 WORDTAG I-PER Rosati
9 WORDTAG O guards
75 WORDTAG O 6-1
9 WORDTAG O gone
29 WORDTAG I-PER Robert
38 WORDTAG O On
5 WORDTAG O prisoners
2 WORDTAG I-ORG office
6 WORDTAG O behalf
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Press
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Tokyo
2 WORDTAG B-MISC Hutu
10 WORDTAG I-LOC Bangladesh
8 WORDTAG O activities
3 WORDTAG I-LOC the
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Petroleum
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Queensland
6 WORDTAG O vowed
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Prize
7 WORDTAG O Princess
5 WORDTAG O posts
16 WORDTAG I-ORG BOSTON
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Toyota
2846 WORDTAG O )
47 WORDTAG O 28
8 WORDTAG I-ORG McLaren
7 WORDTAG O wounds
8 WORDTAG O lunch
258 WORDTAG O government
114 WORDTAG O 21
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Diego
12 WORDTAG O weather
5 WORDTAG I-PER Magdalena
6 WORDTAG O 88
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Bombay
37 WORDTAG O these
5 WORDTAG O narrow
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Hamilton
5 WORDTAG I-PER Phan
5 WORDTAG O everyone
3 WORDTAG I-ORG African
13 WORDTAG I-LOC Wall
29 WORDTAG O 61
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Bombay
1 WORDTAG O Airways
7 WORDTAG O customer
5 WORDTAG O routine
4 WORDTAG I-PER Santos
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Worcestershire
5 WORDTAG O 555
16 WORDTAG O entered
5 WORDTAG O HRW
17 WORDTAG I-LOC Croatia
12 WORDTAG I-MISC Islamic
17 WORDTAG O rules
26 WORDTAG O convention
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Mauritius
6 WORDTAG O seriously
5 WORDTAG I-PER Gingrich
20 WORDTAG O movement
1 WORDTAG I-LOC High
8 WORDTAG I-MISC US$
94 WORDTAG O 1.
8 WORDTAG O blast
5 WORDTAG O clause
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Heathrow
5 WORDTAG I-PER Nilis
7 WORDTAG I-ORG de
5 WORDTAG I-PER Veldman
6 WORDTAG O makers
5 WORDTAG I-PER Hakkinen
17 WORDTAG O visited
9 WORDTAG O values
15 WORDTAG O wicket
2 WORDTAG I-ORG 16
16 WORDTAG I-MISC Series
29 WORDTAG O trip
5 WORDTAG I-PER Lamm
7 WORDTAG O truth
95 WORDTAG O 2.
11 WORDTAG O bodies
30 WORDTAG O old
8 WORDTAG O rivals
14 WORDTAG O bill
29 WORDTAG O captain
10 WORDTAG I-PER Maskhadov
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Eindhoven
32 WORDTAG O free
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Port
5 WORDTAG I-PER Aki
15 WORDTAG I-ORG HOUSTON
8 WORDTAG O lift
8 WORDTAG O landing
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Middlesex
111 WORDTAG O 1996-08-26
280 WORDTAG O million
863 WORDTAG I-MISC _RARE_
36 WORDTAG O might
20 WORDTAG O costs
6 WORDTAG I-PER Nicolas
63 WORDTAG O 1995
6 WORDTAG I-PER Phil
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Buenos
11 WORDTAG I-PER Arantxa
14 WORDTAG O Secretary
12 WORDTAG O session
5 WORDTAG O blown
14 WORDTAG I-LOC HONG
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Lithuania
10 WORDTAG O clash
5 WORDTAG O aboard
24 WORDTAG O 42
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Romanian
5 WORDTAG O meal
9 WORDTAG O markka
6 WORDTAG O hat-trick
5 WORDTAG O achieve
6 WORDTAG I-PER Basuki
16 WORDTAG O seventh
92 WORDTAG O seconds
6 WORDTAG O Chg
5 WORDTAG O importance
14 WORDTAG I-PER Mohammad
5 WORDTAG I-LOC ANGELES
2 WORDTAG O MOODY
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Data
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Union
15 WORDTAG I-LOC Ohio
3 WORDTAG I-MISC Brady
10 WORDTAG O danger
35 WORDTAG O average
28 WORDTAG I-MISC Belgian
5 WORDTAG O spying
6 WORDTAG O believes
14 WORDTAG O factions
27 WORDTAG O TO
13 WORDTAG I-LOC MANCHESTER
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Oklahoma
5 WORDTAG I-PER Mary
11 WORDTAG O Revenue
18 WORDTAG I-LOC Cyprus
57 WORDTAG O rate
8 WORDTAG I-ORG 1860
127 WORDTAG O company
5 WORDTAG O 4221
9 WORDTAG O largely
15 WORDTAG O described
102 WORDTAG O lost
36 WORDTAG O sent
13 WORDTAG I-LOC Street
16 WORDTAG O scores
14 WORDTAG O product
16 WORDTAG O positions
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Kawasaki
30 WORDTAG O yen
31 WORDTAG O fifth
7 WORDTAG I-ORG CNIEC
8 WORDTAG O elected
10 WORDTAG O spring
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Virginia
7 WORDTAG I-PER Roe
6 WORDTAG O abduction
1 WORDTAG O Air
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Glamorgan
15 WORDTAG O 49
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Utrecht
10 WORDTAG O built
6 WORDTAG O themselves
12 WORDTAG O computer
6 WORDTAG O limit
31 WORDTAG O used
5 WORDTAG I-PER Shane
5 WORDTAG O developments
19 WORDTAG I-LOC City
2 WORDTAG I-LOC French
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Spring
68 WORDTAG O country
10 WORDTAG O victim
7 WORDTAG O anyone
22 WORDTAG O As
5 WORDTAG O complex
10 WORDTAG O employee
6 WORDTAG O starter
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Sion
56 WORDTAG O There
18 WORDTAG O appeared
14 WORDTAG O effect
20 WORDTAG O products
6 WORDTAG O 13th
10 WORDTAG O fears
120 WORDTAG O 11
6 WORDTAG O n.a
29 WORDTAG I-LOC Jerusalem
12 WORDTAG O passed
23 WORDTAG O having
7 WORDTAG O hunt
5 WORDTAG O cool
10 WORDTAG O 176
9 WORDTAG O son
13 WORDTAG O broken
15 WORDTAG O starts
105 WORDTAG O made
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Collstrop
3 WORDTAG I-MISC NATIONS
44 WORDTAG O closed
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Federal
10 WORDTAG O worst
8 WORDTAG O goalkeeper
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Nottingham
6 WORDTAG O editorial
10 WORDTAG I-PER Andrew
5 WORDTAG O Pro
44 WORDTAG O 23
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Bogra
10 WORDTAG O huge
330 WORDTAG O which
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Madrid
20 WORDTAG O tonne
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Authority
42 WORDTAG O quarter
2789 WORDTAG O and
6 WORDTAG O bringing
15 WORDTAG O hard
31 WORDTAG O She
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Bremen
5 WORDTAG O sweeping
4 WORDTAG I-PER Edwards
9 WORDTAG I-PER Agassi
24 WORDTAG O economy
3207 WORDTAG I-ORG _RARE_
8 WORDTAG O edged
6 WORDTAG O repeat
5 WORDTAG O heavily
6 WORDTAG O trends
12 WORDTAG O freed
16 WORDTAG O Bowling
6 WORDTAG I-PER Bruguera
186 WORDTAG O or
12 WORDTAG I-PER Levy
5 WORDTAG O span
85 WORDTAG I-LOC Pakistan
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Cardiff
20 WORDTAG I-ORG International
13 WORDTAG I-LOC Los
8 WORDTAG O offers
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Sudan
22 WORDTAG O tax
59 WORDTAG O singles
6 WORDTAG O reopened
7 WORDTAG O pain
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Organisation
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Monaco
5 WORDTAG O lows
7 WORDTAG O timetable
14 WORDTAG O Jul
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Army
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Edwards
41 WORDTAG O fighting
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Port
5 WORDTAG O 9/16
16 WORDTAG O annual
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Dynamo
9 WORDTAG O onto
7 WORDTAG I-PER Ripken
8 WORDTAG O parts
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Rennes
17 WORDTAG I-PER Van
23 WORDTAG O complete
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Bristol
9 WORDTAG I-LOC WELLINGTON
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Wimbledon
47 WORDTAG I-PER Martin
12 WORDTAG O fans
23 WORDTAG O executive
7 WORDTAG O illness
49 WORDTAG O quoted
5 WORDTAG O mainland
19 WORDTAG O increased
9 WORDTAG O fought
5 WORDTAG O walks
45 WORDTAG O announced
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Kerkrade
7 WORDTAG O tied
13 WORDTAG O include
6 WORDTAG O formed
3 WORDTAG I-MISC Jones
6 WORDTAG I-LOC MEXICO
8 WORDTAG O firms
7 WORDTAG O 47th
33 WORDTAG O declared
95 WORDTAG O 3.
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Caribbean
6 WORDTAG O protesters
8 WORDTAG I-PER Pete
5 WORDTAG O sexually
11 WORDTAG I-LOC SEOUL
14 WORDTAG O EPS
7 WORDTAG O Commissioner
7 WORDTAG O commercial
6 WORDTAG O events
8 WORDTAG I-PER O'Neal
9 WORDTAG O According
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Willem
5 WORDTAG O voter
131 WORDTAG O AT
8 WORDTAG O eating
7 WORDTAG O shots
7 WORDTAG O chief-of-staff
20 WORDTAG O involved
17 WORDTAG I-ORG Red
12 WORDTAG O winners
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Division
4 WORDTAG I-LOC Sofia
5 WORDTAG I-PER Preston
8 WORDTAG O seedings
49 WORDTAG O those
30 WORDTAG O *
29 WORDTAG I-ORG Ministry
29 WORDTAG O figures
6 WORDTAG I-PER Fairbrother
6 WORDTAG O radical
21 WORDTAG I-MISC Brazilian
14 WORDTAG O large
14 WORDTAG O shareholders
4 WORDTAG O Price
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Calif.
15 WORDTAG O provide
15 WORDTAG I-ORG ISS
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Cooperation
27 WORDTAG O confirmed
5 WORDTAG O subsidiary
35 WORDTAG O overs
9 WORDTAG I-MISC Jordanian
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Peru
11 WORDTAG I-PER Vicario
5 WORDTAG O experts
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Former
17 WORDTAG I-LOC Venezuela
1 WORDTAG I-MISC President
4 WORDTAG I-LOC NZ
99 WORDTAG O RESULTS
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Birmingham
32 WORDTAG I-MISC Bosnian
17 WORDTAG I-ORG Chicago
5 WORDTAG O stockpile
18 WORDTAG O rival
5 WORDTAG O mistakes
84 WORDTAG O 1/2
5 WORDTAG O medicine
6 WORDTAG O scientists
21 WORDTAG O food
1 WORDTAG I-PER Island
1 WORDTAG B-LOC Israel
1 WORDTAG I-ORG at
27 WORDTAG O pound
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Trinidad
30 WORDTAG O private
2 WORDTAG O Supreme
8 WORDTAG O network
8 WORDTAG O wait
7 WORDTAG I-PER Brooke
12 WORDTAG I-MISC Saudi
7 WORDTAG O trouble
27 WORDTAG O today
35 WORDTAG O period
2 WORDTAG O High
12 WORDTAG O assault
18 WORDTAG O management
10 WORDTAG O longer
8 WORDTAG O lived
5 WORDTAG O bureau
28 WORDTAG I-PER Younis
12 WORDTAG O recovery
85 WORDTAG O news
40 WORDTAG O signed
12 WORDTAG I-ORG OM
9 WORDTAG O homered
16 WORDTAG I-PER Williams
5 WORDTAG O Doctors
15 WORDTAG I-ORG Essex
14 WORDTAG O enough
14 WORDTAG I-ORG Stock
14 WORDTAG O parliamentary
18 WORDTAG O sources
12 WORDTAG I-PER Tsang
7 WORDTAG I-MISC CHAMPIONSHIP
22 WORDTAG I-PER Ian
6 WORDTAG I-PER Damon
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Arequipa
5 WORDTAG I-PER Fogarty
6 WORDTAG O pleased
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Sarajevo
6 WORDTAG I-MISC U.S.-led
16 WORDTAG O measures
1 WORDTAG O II
7 WORDTAG O selling
36 WORDTAG O little
5 WORDTAG O ONE-DAY
5 WORDTAG I-PER Fernandez
84 WORDTAG O metres
10 WORDTAG O view
26 WORDTAG O message
75 WORDTAG O early
5 WORDTAG O 12-year-old
1 WORDTAG I-LOC OF
8 WORDTAG O prosecutors
21 WORDTAG O rain
8 WORDTAG O skull
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Detroit
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Diego
8 WORDTAG I-PER Derek
8 WORDTAG O merger
41 WORDTAG O money
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Centre
6 WORDTAG I-PER An
6 WORDTAG I-PER Capiot
30 WORDTAG I-LOC Argentina
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Angolan
5 WORDTAG O riders
8 WORDTAG O removed
4 WORDTAG I-LOC Soviet
8 WORDTAG O rare
14 WORDTAG I-PER George
1 WORDTAG I-ORG AND
23 WORDTAG I-PER G.
5 WORDTAG O diesel
5 WORDTAG I-LOC SOFIA
20 WORDTAG O included
6 WORDTAG O 64th
9 WORDTAG I-PER Philip
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Office
13 WORDTAG O convicted
7 WORDTAG O strikeouts
5 WORDTAG I-PER Jens
6 WORDTAG O reputation
8 WORDTAG O margins
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Slough
8 WORDTAG I-PER Maleeva
8 WORDTAG I-PER Smith
20 WORDTAG O couple
26 WORDTAG I-PER de
8 WORDTAG O repeatedly
28 WORDTAG O rise
7 WORDTAG O kidnapping
100 WORDTAG O 20
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Liverpool
5 WORDTAG O bottle
48 WORDTAG O IN
29 WORDTAG O An
8 WORDTAG O apparently
98 WORDTAG O back
13 WORDTAG I-PER Moin
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Euro
7 WORDTAG O balls
6 WORDTAG O families
57 WORDTAG O 60
11 WORDTAG O distribution
147 WORDTAG O week
6 WORDTAG O 1,500
6 WORDTAG O understanding
5 WORDTAG I-PER Klinsmann
14 WORDTAG I-LOC Malta
9 WORDTAG O earned
18 WORDTAG O believe
36 WORDTAG O 're
11 WORDTAG O however
11 WORDTAG O mother
6 WORDTAG O equivalent
50 WORDTAG I-PER David
7 WORDTAG I-PER El
39 WORDTAG O 40
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Hong
109 WORDTAG O President
6 WORDTAG I-PER Anderson
111 WORDTAG O him
48 WORDTAG I-ORG United
45 WORDTAG O work
7 WORDTAG O copies
6 WORDTAG I-ORG India
5 WORDTAG I-ORG TV
72 WORDTAG O foreign
9 WORDTAG O knew
9 WORDTAG O field
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Philip
10 WORDTAG O sprint
10 WORDTAG O proposal
15 WORDTAG O consumer
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Tamil
18 WORDTAG O bln
14 WORDTAG O join
25 WORDTAG O parties
87 WORDTAG I-LOC Japan
8 WORDTAG O hijacking
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Islamic
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Boston
13 WORDTAG O newspapers
66 WORDTAG O 1996-08-24
62 WORDTAG I-LOC Republic
12 WORDTAG O resume
3 WORDTAG I-MISC 310
5 WORDTAG O 12th
29 WORDTAG O forecast
1 WORDTAG I-PER Royal
9 WORDTAG O lose
11 WORDTAG O 199
37 WORDTAG O club
5 WORDTAG O 5/8
8 WORDTAG O handling
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Stuttgart
6 WORDTAG O renewed
8 WORDTAG O none
98 WORDTAG O shares
6 WORDTAG I-MISC serie
7 WORDTAG O camp
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Russian
7 WORDTAG I-PER Baker
5 WORDTAG O set-top
5 WORDTAG I-PER Broadhurst
7 WORDTAG I-PER Billy
5 WORDTAG O demonstrators
40 WORDTAG O scored
8 WORDTAG O station
36 WORDTAG O ban
8 WORDTAG O try
5 WORDTAG I-PER Grant
8 WORDTAG O 85
9 WORDTAG O inflation
5 WORDTAG O ordering
5 WORDTAG O contest
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Pittsburgh
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Warburg
23 WORDTAG O 46
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Charleroi
7 WORDTAG O cup
8 WORDTAG I-MISC New
5 WORDTAG O farms
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Treaty
3 WORDTAG I-PER Goldman
48 WORDTAG O OF
58 WORDTAG O 72
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Interior
4 WORDTAG I-LOC Seoul
6 WORDTAG O kingdom
7 WORDTAG I-PER Eriksson
6 WORDTAG O District
5 WORDTAG O procedure
29 WORDTAG I-LOC Egypt
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Costa
42 WORDTAG I-LOC Finland
17 WORDTAG O adding
6 WORDTAG I-PER Anke
45 WORDTAG O whether
41 WORDTAG I-MISC Olympic
10 WORDTAG I-LOC Slovenia
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Defence
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Damascus
7 WORDTAG O nations
7 WORDTAG O strikers
10 WORDTAG O New
17 WORDTAG I-PER Cork
1 WORDTAG I-ORG 1
14 WORDTAG O threatened
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Angels
5 WORDTAG I-PER Sharpe
4 WORDTAG I-LOC US
7221 WORDTAG O the
8 WORDTAG I-PER Sven
7 WORDTAG O RALLYING
6 WORDTAG O Operating
16 WORDTAG I-ORG KANSAS
5 WORDTAG O therapy
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Canberra
3 WORDTAG I-PER Arthur
6 WORDTAG O legislature
5 WORDTAG O sheet
29 WORDTAG O groups
93 WORDTAG I-LOC LONDON
9 WORDTAG I-PER Kocinski
8 WORDTAG O postponed
9 WORDTAG I-PER Tillstrom
34 WORDTAG O Aug
9 WORDTAG O population
7 WORDTAG O margin
9 WORDTAG I-PER Angel
15 WORDTAG I-ORG Feyenoord
6 WORDTAG O supporting
136 WORDTAG O between
5 WORDTAG O 87
24 WORDTAG O Net
15 WORDTAG I-MISC War
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Biogen
10 WORDTAG O 4.0
14 WORDTAG I-PER Craig
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Tankan
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Universe
9 WORDTAG O suicide
5 WORDTAG O contacts
5 WORDTAG I-PER Henry
5 WORDTAG O negotiated
25 WORDTAG O attacks
45 WORDTAG I-LOC Kong
2 WORDTAG O Information
10 WORDTAG O hotel
10 WORDTAG I-PER Saddam
8 WORDTAG O 4-3
30 WORDTAG O 48
10 WORDTAG O crude
6 WORDTAG I-PER Dimitris
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Hanwha
9 WORDTAG O rises
10 WORDTAG O heroin
7 WORDTAG I-PER Alberto
9 WORDTAG I-PER Ronald
5 WORDTAG O nurses
12 WORDTAG I-MISC Nations
25 WORDTAG O After
1 WORDTAG B-MISC Jewish
335 WORDTAG O beat
44 WORDTAG O 65
24 WORDTAG O big
6 WORDTAG O operate
9 WORDTAG I-PER Takeda
5 WORDTAG O ordinary
30 WORDTAG I-ORG YORK
2 WORDTAG I-LOC PHILADELPHIA
8 WORDTAG O presidency
30 WORDTAG I-ORG NEW
2 WORDTAG I-MISC Ferrari
24 WORDTAG O great
10 WORDTAG O delay
5 WORDTAG I-PER Azharuddin
6 WORDTAG O sharply
8 WORDTAG I-PER Aoki
7 WORDTAG O secured
4 WORDTAG I-LOC Dublin
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Vale
6 WORDTAG O self-rule
15 WORDTAG O delayed
4 WORDTAG I-PER Allenby
27 WORDTAG O playing
14 WORDTAG O fiscal
15 WORDTAG I-ORG FRANCISCO
4 WORDTAG I-ORG In
49 WORDTAG I-ORG Party
40 WORDTAG O STANDINGS
7 WORDTAG I-PER Anthony
5 WORDTAG O retail
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Frankfurt
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Waalwijk
10 WORDTAG O intervention
9 WORDTAG O two-run
12 WORDTAG O 4-1
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Indians
22 WORDTAG O player
71 WORDTAG O 22
6 WORDTAG O resulted
6 WORDTAG O resort
2 WORDTAG I-LOC SOUTH
5 WORDTAG O nationalist
5 WORDTAG O listed
23 WORDTAG O poll
1 WORDTAG I-MISC and
8 WORDTAG I-PER Monica
21 WORDTAG O school
9 WORDTAG I-PER Perot
26 WORDTAG O reached
6 WORDTAG O amnesty
5 WORDTAG O .457
8 WORDTAG O changes
6 WORDTAG O fatal
1 WORDTAG I-ORG alliance
12 WORDTAG O inside
8 WORDTAG I-LOC Midwest
14 WORDTAG O done
1 WORDTAG I-ORG AS
6 WORDTAG O explained
5 WORDTAG O 35th
16 WORDTAG I-LOC California
35 WORDTAG O me
5 WORDTAG O semifinalist
18 WORDTAG O stop
38 WORDTAG O own
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Samsung
6 WORDTAG I-PER Justin
40 WORDTAG O much
62 WORDTAG O same
10 WORDTAG O decide
9 WORDTAG O southeast
7 WORDTAG O putting
1 WORDTAG I-ORG MANCHESTER
6 WORDTAG O retailer
28 WORDTAG O force
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Affairs
8 WORDTAG O candidates
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Irish
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Morris
12 WORDTAG O grain
44 WORDTAG O parliament
45 WORDTAG O election
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Christopher
128 WORDTAG O played
5 WORDTAG O titles
32 WORDTAG O standings
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Stuttgart
8 WORDTAG I-MISC Czech
8 WORDTAG O Soyoil
23 WORDTAG O low
6 WORDTAG O 2,000
12 WORDTAG O something
209 WORDTAG O He
7 WORDTAG O forest
10 WORDTAG O care
5 WORDTAG O 900
5 WORDTAG I-ORG OJ
12 WORDTAG I-LOC JERUSALEM
9 WORDTAG O SEP
8 WORDTAG O accepted
9 WORDTAG O friend
7 WORDTAG O suspicion
5 WORDTAG I-LOC BOGOTA
1 WORDTAG I-PER Vale
6 WORDTAG I-PER Kornblum
5 WORDTAG O insistence
8 WORDTAG O possibility
19 WORDTAG O 10th
13 WORDTAG I-LOC Saudi
14 WORDTAG I-PER Andrea
10 WORDTAG O considering
12 WORDTAG O While
41 WORDTAG O taken
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Groningen
71 WORDTAG O can
5 WORDTAG O strikes
22 WORDTAG O banks
12 WORDTAG O Summary
5 WORDTAG I-PER Hogg
6 WORDTAG O command
13 WORDTAG O begin
8 WORDTAG O cleared
25 WORDTAG O aggregate
7 WORDTAG O NOTES
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Wisconsin
7 WORDTAG O review
1 WORDTAG I-ORG UK
13 WORDTAG O +31
7 WORDTAG I-PER Teutenberg
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Nyva
6 WORDTAG I-ORG LME
18 WORDTAG I-ORG Rangers
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Monaco
15 WORDTAG I-MISC Korean
8 WORDTAG O absence
5 WORDTAG O 389
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Tilburg
25 WORDTAG O 45
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Melbourne
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Sierra
23 WORDTAG O 326
9 WORDTAG O 125
14 WORDTAG I-ORG Sox
12 WORDTAG O Although
8 WORDTAG O noise
8 WORDTAG O RACING
4 WORDTAG O Ministry
24 WORDTAG O 2-6
100 WORDTAG O world
12 WORDTAG O questioned
6 WORDTAG O Security
13 WORDTAG O speak
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Ireland
5 WORDTAG O pills
5 WORDTAG O bounce
1 WORDTAG O Hamlet
17 WORDTAG I-LOC Zimbabwe
19 WORDTAG O legal
6 WORDTAG I-PER Hope
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Graafschap
64 WORDTAG I-LOC Netherlands
5 WORDTAG O tanks
11 WORDTAG I-PER Gough
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Chesterfield
9 WORDTAG O executed
18 WORDTAG I-ORG Interfax
192 WORDTAG O Monday
18 WORDTAG I-ORG Amsterdam
10 WORDTAG O kg
6 WORDTAG O invitation
8 WORDTAG O emerged
7 WORDTAG O signing
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Baltimore
9 WORDTAG I-MISC Islamists
5 WORDTAG O shutdown
2 WORDTAG I-ORG RBI
1 WORDTAG I-PER Singer
6 WORDTAG O surrender
12 WORDTAG O soldier
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Arminia
38 WORDTAG O region
13 WORDTAG I-ORG Cincinnati
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Swindon
4 WORDTAG O 21st
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Astros
15 WORDTAG O heart
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Warsaw
5 WORDTAG O laps
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Jerusalem
6 WORDTAG O dated
6 WORDTAG O .538
7 WORDTAG I-ORG SV
1 WORDTAG I-ORG motor
37 WORDTAG O died
0 WORDTAG B-ORG _RARE_
23 WORDTAG O decided
13 WORDTAG I-MISC Spanish
8 WORDTAG I-ORG PLO
120 WORDTAG O match
5 WORDTAG O Premier
5 WORDTAG O Asked
1 WORDTAG I-ORG do
13 WORDTAG O issued
11 WORDTAG I-LOC Kremlin
16 WORDTAG O water
13 WORDTAG O accident
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Vermont
5 WORDTAG O substantial
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Petroleum
5 WORDTAG I-PER Kucera
6 WORDTAG O relay
16 WORDTAG I-PER Graf
11 WORDTAG O retired
5 WORDTAG O portfolio
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Colombian
18 WORDTAG O drew
5 WORDTAG I-PER Kaluwitharana
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Charity
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Shanghai
13 WORDTAG O debate
10 WORDTAG O quite
6 WORDTAG O beyond
5 WORDTAG I-PER Eddie
6 WORDTAG I-PER Johansson
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Salomon
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Durham
2 WORDTAG O Industry
6 WORDTAG O wages
8 WORDTAG I-PER Charles
11 WORDTAG O using
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Desk
10 WORDTAG O relief
8 WORDTAG I-LOC Rome
10 WORDTAG I-PER Corser
5 WORDTAG O fairly
8 WORDTAG I-PER Slight
8 WORDTAG I-MISC Russians
15 WORDTAG I-ORG CALIFORNIA
3 WORDTAG O Club
5 WORDTAG I-PER Guzman
5 WORDTAG I-PER Wang
7 WORDTAG O affected
13 WORDTAG O weaker
5 WORDTAG O 11.00
24 WORDTAG O treaty
9 WORDTAG O dollars
5 WORDTAG O div
11 WORDTAG O surplus
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Wall
1 WORDTAG B-MISC Roman
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Hamilton
8 WORDTAG O remove
13 WORDTAG O accept
13 WORDTAG O east
15 WORDTAG I-PER Peres
6 WORDTAG O citizen
7 WORDTAG O X
8 WORDTAG O ousted
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Gingrich
14 WORDTAG O 6-7
7 WORDTAG O hear
5 WORDTAG O Nearly
5 WORDTAG O thanks
13 WORDTAG O investigators
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Queen
5 WORDTAG O Five
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Notts
1 WORDTAG B-MISC Rwandan
15 WORDTAG I-PER Morris
21 WORDTAG O federal
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Petra
5 WORDTAG O setting
7 WORDTAG O 12.
8 WORDTAG O 106
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Oklahoma
11 WORDTAG I-ORG IVAC
9 WORDTAG I-MISC Hungarian
50 WORDTAG O place
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Labour
6 WORDTAG I-MISC CANADIAN
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Ligier
10 WORDTAG O bilateral
60 WORDTAG O man
33 WORDTAG O bonds
50 WORDTAG O CRICKET
9 WORDTAG O weak
9 WORDTAG I-PER Makinen
49 WORDTAG I-MISC Israeli
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Freiburg
7 WORDTAG I-PER Reeve
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Robert
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Everton
28 WORDTAG O seeding
9 WORDTAG O Group
17 WORDTAG O farm
4 WORDTAG I-MISC Subaru
7 WORDTAG O motor
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Pacific
2 WORDTAG O Court
12 WORDTAG I-PER Inzamam-ul-Haq
1 WORDTAG O Max
3 WORDTAG O Defence
9 WORDTAG O throughout
6 WORDTAG O corn
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Arthur
7 WORDTAG I-PER Jon
2 WORDTAG I-LOC )
4 WORDTAG O 310
16 WORDTAG O admitted
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Air
18 WORDTAG O relations
5 WORDTAG O sure
13 WORDTAG I-LOC Angeles
5 WORDTAG I-PER Donovan
2 WORDTAG I-PER Dundee
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Nancy
14 WORDTAG O cases
6 WORDTAG I-MISC ITALIAN
9 WORDTAG O spend
14 WORDTAG O truce
5 WORDTAG O mutual
501 WORDTAG O have
1 WORDTAG O Radio
29 WORDTAG I-LOC Nigeria
10 WORDTAG I-LOC Estonia
5 WORDTAG I-ORG General
11 WORDTAG O county
6 WORDTAG O Latest
6 WORDTAG I-PER Shimon
60 WORDTAG O then
6 WORDTAG O directed
17 WORDTAG O deals
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Investors
8 WORDTAG I-PER Collinelli
5 WORDTAG O 278
5 WORDTAG O stole
12 WORDTAG I-LOC Doboj
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Van
5 WORDTAG O 19th
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Bucharest
4 WORDTAG I-MISC on
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Tirana
10 WORDTAG I-LOC Ethiopia
6 WORDTAG I-ORG PTT
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Power
55 WORDTAG O good
2 WORDTAG I-ORG V
7 WORDTAG O speed
7 WORDTAG O attended
8 WORDTAG I-ORG SPLA
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Christian
29 WORDTAG O latest
7 WORDTAG O ------------------------
11 WORDTAG O riots
98 WORDTAG O if
5 WORDTAG O TUESDAY
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Spain
86 WORDTAG O being
57 WORDTAG I-LOC States
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Delhi
24 WORDTAG O returned
19 WORDTAG I-PER Scott
5 WORDTAG O rankings
8 WORDTAG O stood
8 WORDTAG I-MISC Iraqis
5 WORDTAG O buyers
12 WORDTAG I-LOC Hospital
99 WORDTAG O September
5 WORDTAG O returns
5 WORDTAG O crossing
5 WORDTAG O handgun
2 WORDTAG I-MISC SOUTH
5 WORDTAG O weakening
5 WORDTAG O 11-6
33 WORDTAG O public
6 WORDTAG I-PER Akam
24 WORDTAG O denied
8 WORDTAG O first-round
19 WORDTAG O November
12 WORDTAG I-PER Pedro
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Central
7 WORDTAG I-LOC GENEVA
5 WORDTAG I-MISC TOSHIBA
15 WORDTAG O proposed
24 WORDTAG O too
6 WORDTAG O terrorism
12 WORDTAG O 5.0
1406 WORDTAG O for
23 WORDTAG O line
25 WORDTAG I-ORG Exchange
14 WORDTAG O live
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Board
17 WORDTAG O WIN
1 WORDTAG O Golf
8 WORDTAG O Now
68 WORDTAG O visit
45 WORDTAG I-LOC Hong
10 WORDTAG O policemen
6 WORDTAG O appears
21 WORDTAG O 171
9 WORDTAG O delivered
6 WORDTAG O develop
199 WORDTAG O new
39 WORDTAG I-LOC Ukraine
8 WORDTAG O task
10 WORDTAG O effort
5 WORDTAG O partnership
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Peace
293 WORDTAG O year
9 WORDTAG O Did
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Monde
16 WORDTAG I-MISC CENTRAL
11 WORDTAG O turn
6 WORDTAG O getting
7 WORDTAG I-PER K.
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Arnhem
8 WORDTAG I-PER Darren
5 WORDTAG I-PER Stefano
46 WORDTAG O 26
23 WORDTAG O continued
6 WORDTAG O nun
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Havre
9 WORDTAG O 15,000
51 WORDTAG O start
11 WORDTAG O Three
1 WORDTAG O University
18 WORDTAG I-LOC Nepal
5 WORDTAG O pinch-hitter
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Stirling
20 WORDTAG O currency
18 WORDTAG O territory
5 WORDTAG I-PER Adams
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Gas
7 WORDTAG O hearing
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Hill
6 WORDTAG O explain
5 WORDTAG O ALERT
8 WORDTAG I-PER Brian
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Brussels
9 WORDTAG I-PER Brunswijk
5 WORDTAG O aiming
9 WORDTAG I-PER der
5 WORDTAG O STAGE
4 WORDTAG I-PER Abu
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Indians
9 WORDTAG O social
21 WORDTAG O appeal
7 WORDTAG O escape
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Liberation
11 WORDTAG O considered
15 WORDTAG O travel
5 WORDTAG O dictator
8 WORDTAG O connection
93 WORDTAG I-PER Clinton
14 WORDTAG I-ORG Motorola
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Wales
6 WORDTAG O sparked
169 WORDTAG O her
12 WORDTAG O evidence
9 WORDTAG O cycling
11 WORDTAG O flew
16 WORDTAG O bus
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Melbourne
7 WORDTAG O fun
6 WORDTAG I-PER Kubo
6 WORDTAG O pilot
9 WORDTAG O planning
5 WORDTAG O Interior
9 WORDTAG I-PER Olsza
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Kuwait
9 WORDTAG I-MISC Java
8 WORDTAG O magazines
9 WORDTAG O counterpart
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Johnson
28 WORDTAG I-ORG PSV
5 WORDTAG O fields
171 WORDTAG O In
43 WORDTAG O went
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Cambridge
19 WORDTAG O sixth
17 WORDTAG I-LOC San
6 WORDTAG I-MISC Norwegian
10 WORDTAG O opens
9 WORDTAG O lawsuit
5 WORDTAG O 107
5 WORDTAG O apiece
6 WORDTAG O express
4 WORDTAG O P
8 WORDTAG I-MISC AMERICAN
3 WORDTAG I-MISC Kong
45 WORDTAG O loss
8 WORDTAG O maintain
10 WORDTAG O build
55 WORDTAG O 16
17 WORDTAG I-ORG Paris
10 WORDTAG O pts
8 WORDTAG O concerns
4 WORDTAG O 162
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Net
48 WORDTAG O women
13 WORDTAG O account
12 WORDTAG O diplomats
11 WORDTAG I-ORG South
10 WORDTAG O 110
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Bastia
5 WORDTAG O plantation
5 WORDTAG O effectively
12 WORDTAG O candidate
5 WORDTAG O 6.5
21 WORDTAG O plant
6 WORDTAG I-PER Juha
15 WORDTAG O bat
12 WORDTAG O software
37 WORDTAG O again
14 WORDTAG I-PER Greg
14 WORDTAG O role
37 WORDTAG O control
2 WORDTAG O Street
14 WORDTAG O 33
2 WORDTAG I-MISC Law
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Massachusetts
11 WORDTAG I-PER Frank
1418 WORDTAG O 1
18 WORDTAG O post
11 WORDTAG O faction
5 WORDTAG O allied
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Suwon
48 WORDTAG O already
7 WORDTAG O staged
5 WORDTAG O reigning
23 WORDTAG O bid
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Home
36 WORDTAG O does
19 WORDTAG O ball
28 WORDTAG O soon
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Arab
56 WORDTAG O Men
12 WORDTAG I-MISC Algerian
14 WORDTAG O suspected
21 WORDTAG I-LOC Hungary
5 WORDTAG O instructions
144 WORDTAG O time
12 WORDTAG O show
3 WORDTAG I-MISC NEC
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Bordeaux
19 WORDTAG O Division
25 WORDTAG O ground
8 WORDTAG O baht
9 WORDTAG O 150
11 WORDTAG O gained
2036 WORDTAG O on
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Congress
6 WORDTAG I-PER Tommi
18 WORDTAG O soldiers
303 WORDTAG O percent
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Tranmere
29 WORDTAG O got
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Duesseldorf
9 WORDTAG I-ORG White
5 WORDTAG O window
5 WORDTAG O decisive
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Frankfurt
9 WORDTAG I-LOC BEIJING
6 WORDTAG O athletes
28 WORDTAG I-LOC Iran
9 WORDTAG O nomination
20 WORDTAG I-MISC Thai
8 WORDTAG O ceremony
20 WORDTAG O His
21 WORDTAG I-PER Richard
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Rovers
8 WORDTAG O gets
6 WORDTAG O unfortunate
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Journal
6 WORDTAG I-PER Mikael
10 WORDTAG O Deputy
14 WORDTAG I-MISC Argentine
4 WORDTAG I-LOC Northern
6 WORDTAG O easy
1 WORDTAG I-ORG bank
1 WORDTAG O News
8 WORDTAG O falling
120 WORDTAG O off
1 WORDTAG I-LOC MILWAUKEE
20 WORDTAG I-ORG Honda
10 WORDTAG O scattered
3382 WORDTAG O to
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Texas
13 WORDTAG O AFTER
5 WORDTAG O load
10 WORDTAG O witnesses
1 WORDTAG O Championship
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Khan
22 WORDTAG O important
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Queens
7 WORDTAG O exact
1 WORDTAG I-LOC La
38 WORDTAG I-LOC Sri
5 WORDTAG O YEAR-AGO
6 WORDTAG O Despite
5 WORDTAG O soybeans
3 WORDTAG I-MISC HONG
9 WORDTAG O addition
88 WORDTAG I-LOC Russia
16 WORDTAG O accuracy
9 WORDTAG I-LOC of
4 WORDTAG I-MISC Nepali
1 WORDTAG O Van
8 WORDTAG O CAPS
1 WORDTAG O Reserve
5 WORDTAG O ACTUAL
69 WORDTAG O 50
4 WORDTAG I-LOC Hamburg
2 WORDTAG O Press
22 WORDTAG O dead
11 WORDTAG O estimates
21 WORDTAG I-PER Mother
5 WORDTAG O +7095
17 WORDTAG I-LOC MOSCOW
15 WORDTAG O avoid
40 WORDTAG O rights
285 WORDTAG O Thursday
6 WORDTAG O rice
71 WORDTAG O political
5 WORDTAG O telling
10 WORDTAG O threw
36 WORDTAG O right
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Portuguese
71 WORDTAG O per
6 WORDTAG O sound
29 WORDTAG O result
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Star
8 WORDTAG O backing
6 WORDTAG I-ORG IOC
61 WORDTAG I-LOC London
14 WORDTAG O emergency
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Salang
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Nepal
6 WORDTAG O follows
7 WORDTAG O professional
14 WORDTAG I-ORG AG
8 WORDTAG I-PER Jayasuriya
14 WORDTAG O launched
6 WORDTAG O slam
29 WORDTAG O human
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Villa
21 WORDTAG O drugs
11 WORDTAG O threatening
7 WORDTAG I-PER Botham
18 WORDTAG O defender
13 WORDTAG O ROUND
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Our
5 WORDTAG O Close
6 WORDTAG O erupted
9 WORDTAG O someone
2 WORDTAG I-PER Angeles
15 WORDTAG I-ORG CLEVELAND
11 WORDTAG O written
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Doetinchem
7 WORDTAG O threats
17 WORDTAG I-LOC Yugoslavia
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Breda
7 WORDTAG O abuse
10 WORDTAG O brief
5 WORDTAG I-PER Heeswijk
11 WORDTAG O 15-11
5 WORDTAG O genocide
6 WORDTAG O pursuit
22 WORDTAG O turned
15 WORDTAG I-ORG Le
50 WORDTAG O sales
1 WORDTAG I-MISC 162
8 WORDTAG O neighbours
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Jordan
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Middle
28 WORDTAG I-MISC Republican
11 WORDTAG O =
15 WORDTAG I-PER Marcelo
8 WORDTAG O advanced
31 WORDTAG O face
18 WORDTAG O truck
5 WORDTAG O withdrew
2 WORDTAG I-PER Edouard
18 WORDTAG O evening
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Czech
9 WORDTAG O stepped
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Brush
8 WORDTAG O calling
13 WORDTAG I-MISC Sri
5 WORDTAG O establish
7 WORDTAG O judicial
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Bridge
14 WORDTAG O ending
19 WORDTAG I-PER R.
10 WORDTAG O confidence
14 WORDTAG O pulled
70 WORDTAG I-ORG Newsroom
8 WORDTAG I-MISC Lakes
8 WORDTAG O establishment
110 WORDTAG O next
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Atlantic
27 WORDTAG O rule
47 WORDTAG O central
36 WORDTAG O fourth
1 WORDTAG I-PER Roman
23 WORDTAG O fall
5 WORDTAG O coup
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Community
12 WORDTAG O abandoned
7 WORDTAG O store
6 WORDTAG O 212-859-1650
1 WORDTAG I-MISC States
284 WORDTAG O this
11 WORDTAG O spoke
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Queensland
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Gloria
6 WORDTAG O multiple
19 WORDTAG I-ORG Democratic
83 WORDTAG O earlier
3 WORDTAG I-PER Lotte
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Young
30 WORDTAG I-LOC Europe
6 WORDTAG O extended
15 WORDTAG I-ORG /
13 WORDTAG O 15-12
7 WORDTAG O theft
30 WORDTAG O showed
5 WORDTAG I-PER Ferrigato
7 WORDTAG O criminal
56 WORDTAG O Prime
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Parma
6 WORDTAG O remote
5 WORDTAG O praised
89 WORDTAG O month
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Allenby
12 WORDTAG I-ORG American
130 WORDTAG I-LOC Australia
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Genoa
16 WORDTAG O preliminary
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Missionaries
6 WORDTAG O outperform
42 WORDTAG O 1997
1 WORDTAG I-ORG French
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Odra
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Vatican
6 WORDTAG O 85th
19 WORDTAG O bad
25 WORDTAG O 2-1
6 WORDTAG O churches
34 WORDTAG I-ORG Ajax
64 WORDTAG I-LOC Africa
21 WORDTAG O negotiations
5 WORDTAG I-PER Vacek
17 WORDTAG O With
44 WORDTAG O return
1 WORDTAG I-PER Poland
64 WORDTAG O 6.
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Police
6 WORDTAG O 266
21 WORDTAG I-PER Lewis
7 WORDTAG O confirm
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Volendam
13 WORDTAG O revised
2 WORDTAG I-LOC County
15 WORDTAG O THE
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Middlesbrough
56 WORDTAG O issue
7 WORDTAG I-PER Evert
11 WORDTAG O expressed
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Warwickshire
12 WORDTAG O employees
9 WORDTAG I-LOC BELGRADE
6 WORDTAG O killer
5 WORDTAG O 4-95
7 WORDTAG O overseas
32 WORDTAG O trying
6 WORDTAG I-ORG VfB
10 WORDTAG O apartheid
1 WORDTAG I-PER Polonia
19 WORDTAG O career
14 WORDTAG O secret
14 WORDTAG I-ORG MONTREAL
5 WORDTAG I-PER Palkhivala
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Chorzow
85 WORDTAG O division
15 WORDTAG O boy
15 WORDTAG O am
3 WORDTAG I-LOC coast
14 WORDTAG O starting
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Philadelphia
8 WORDTAG O runner-up
6 WORDTAG O Match
8 WORDTAG O stores
3 WORDTAG I-PER Field
6 WORDTAG O edge
18 WORDTAG O suffered
19 WORDTAG O offered
6 WORDTAG I-PER Korda
12 WORDTAG I-ORG LG
1 WORDTAG I-MISC S&P
6 WORDTAG O affect
5 WORDTAG O rubber
17 WORDTAG O More
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Detroit
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Australia
109 WORDTAG O former
55 WORDTAG O minister
13 WORDTAG O imports
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Manchester
6 WORDTAG I-MISC CAC-40
8 WORDTAG I-PER Javier
14 WORDTAG I-PER Jason
9 WORDTAG O Qualifier
6 WORDTAG I-MISC Spaniard
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Sauber
47 WORDTAG I-PER Arafat
8 WORDTAG O produce
7 WORDTAG O reserves
7 WORDTAG O internal
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Mariners
5 WORDTAG I-PER Howard
9 WORDTAG I-PER Roger
5 WORDTAG O criticised
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Somerset
28 WORDTAG I-PER Croft
5 WORDTAG O roubles
38 WORDTAG O campaign
8 WORDTAG I-LOC de
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Zealand
21 WORDTAG I-PER Jim
12 WORDTAG O 15-6
5 WORDTAG O usual
5 WORDTAG I-PER Mia
14 WORDTAG O filed
7 WORDTAG O hundreds
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Europe
13 WORDTAG O imposed
144 WORDTAG O than
9 WORDTAG I-LOC Liberia
10 WORDTAG O read
6 WORDTAG O limits
10 WORDTAG I-PER Max
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Greece
6 WORDTAG O personal
198 WORDTAG O A
31 WORDTAG O industry
11 WORDTAG O bottom
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Democracy
31 WORDTAG I-MISC Democratic
6 WORDTAG I-MISC Classic
6 WORDTAG O acquired
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Daewoo
42 WORDTAG O morning
5 WORDTAG I-PER Blind
757 WORDTAG O from
45 WORDTAG O 19
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Vienna
6 WORDTAG O FROM
10 WORDTAG I-MISC Catholic
19 WORDTAG I-ORG FC
5 WORDTAG O follow
6 WORDTAG O stand
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Antwerp
9 WORDTAG O cross
49 WORDTAG O demand
13 WORDTAG I-LOC Paulo
2 WORDTAG I-ORG McCarthy
5 WORDTAG I-PER Alami
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Bradford
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Arab
9 WORDTAG O vehicle
9 WORDTAG O THIRD
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Dutch
12 WORDTAG O managed
17 WORDTAG O largest
11 WORDTAG I-LOC Dhaka
25 WORDTAG O island
5 WORDTAG O tree
5 WORDTAG O require
5 WORDTAG O 859
100 WORDTAG O 6-2
27 WORDTAG O coming
6 WORDTAG I-LOC S.
7 WORDTAG I-MISC BELGIAN
1 WORDTAG B-MISC Most
7 WORDTAG O plants
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Vaduz
28 WORDTAG O unless
51 WORDTAG O another
5 WORDTAG O films
2 WORDTAG O Stock
25 WORDTAG O prefix
7 WORDTAG O equaliser
40 WORDTAG O hits
36 WORDTAG O ceasefire
25 WORDTAG I-PER Netanyahu
5 WORDTAG I-PER Specter
9 WORDTAG O replace
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Republican
3 WORDTAG I-MISC Division
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Central
1 WORDTAG O GRAND
5 WORDTAG I-MISC post-Soviet
8 WORDTAG O aged
9 WORDTAG O doubles
102 WORDTAG O 14
5 WORDTAG O paint
110 WORDTAG I-LOC Spain
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Davis
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Add
12 WORDTAG O leadership
7 WORDTAG I-PER Yoshikawa
6 WORDTAG O units
13 WORDTAG I-LOC Lebanon
7 WORDTAG O 8.0
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Park
4 WORDTAG I-PER Wolf
1 WORDTAG O OFFICIAL
6 WORDTAG O arrests
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Ipswich
388 WORDTAG O first
6 WORDTAG B-ORG Greens
21 WORDTAG I-LOC Scotland
5 WORDTAG O meets
2 WORDTAG I-PER Wall
15 WORDTAG I-ORG TORONTO
5 WORDTAG I-PER Rifkind
8 WORDTAG O prospects
5 WORDTAG O 3/4
5 WORDTAG I-PER Bedie
8 WORDTAG O gunman
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Tyrrell
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Mideast
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Research
16 WORDTAG O cooperation
14 WORDTAG O students
10 WORDTAG O five-year
7 WORDTAG O abuses
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Trent
6 WORDTAG O allow
8 WORDTAG I-LOC HOUSTON
1 WORDTAG I-LOC ,
13 WORDTAG I-PER Lauck
5 WORDTAG O negotiator
5 WORDTAG O By
5 WORDTAG O save
17 WORDTAG I-ORG Service
20 WORDTAG O steady
13 WORDTAG I-LOC Sao
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Rostock
8 WORDTAG O Oct
13 WORDTAG O west
7 WORDTAG O embargo
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Alaska
8 WORDTAG O CHAMPIONSHIP
7 WORDTAG O 4,000
6 WORDTAG O pitched
17 WORDTAG O arrest
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Lotte
7 WORDTAG I-PER Kabariti
61 WORDTAG O close
7 WORDTAG O sentence
30 WORDTAG O That
46 WORDTAG O authorities
4 WORDTAG I-ORG District
2 WORDTAG I-ORG States
5 WORDTAG O representing
28 WORDTAG O halftime
8 WORDTAG I-ORG AZ
134 WORDTAG O years
11 WORDTAG O 4-0
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Gatwick
4 WORDTAG I-MISC Costa
18 WORDTAG O officers
6 WORDTAG O compatriot
21 WORDTAG O air
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Dan
12 WORDTAG I-ORG California
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Arkansas
14 WORDTAG O approved
1 WORDTAG I-MISC BRUSSELS
2 WORDTAG I-MISC .
12 WORDTAG O contact
15 WORDTAG I-ORG Moscow
5 WORDTAG O acres
5 WORDTAG I-ORG League
6 WORDTAG I-LOC U.S
9 WORDTAG O custody
8 WORDTAG O program
95 WORDTAG I-MISC Russian
49 WORDTAG I-PER Ahmed
36 WORDTAG O give
12 WORDTAG O 50,000
3 WORDTAG I-PER Petra
9 WORDTAG O response
9 WORDTAG O equal
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Bistrita
26 WORDTAG O independence
8 WORDTAG O resign
14 WORDTAG O performance
137 WORDTAG O points
10 WORDTAG O research
15 WORDTAG I-ORG San
11 WORDTAG I-PER Boardman
8 WORDTAG O inches
15 WORDTAG O efforts
6 WORDTAG O yards
9 WORDTAG O 7-3
33 WORDTAG I-LOC Bosnia
5 WORDTAG I-PER Rohrabacher
16 WORDTAG O family
2 WORDTAG I-LOC Montreal
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Reform
68 WORDTAG O champion
5 WORDTAG I-ORG THE
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Khmer
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Black
10 WORDTAG O fly
6 WORDTAG O reply
5 WORDTAG O investigations
7 WORDTAG I-PER McGrath
38 WORDTAG O recent
9 WORDTAG I-ORG Karlsruhe
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Angeles
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Lebanon
12 WORDTAG O incident
9 WORDTAG O cement
5 WORDTAG O mines
22 WORDTAG O committee
6 WORDTAG I-PER Berger
6 WORDTAG O hostages
10 WORDTAG O cause
5 WORDTAG O metal
6 WORDTAG O 111
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Law
10 WORDTAG O GDP
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Sakigake
10 WORDTAG O add
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Gulf
7 WORDTAG O waste
16 WORDTAG I-PER Chang
12 WORDTAG O WORLD
8 WORDTAG O volatility
10 WORDTAG O reason
972 WORDTAG O 2
5 WORDTAG I-ORG LTTE
45 WORDTAG I-ORG Commission
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Angels
8 WORDTAG I-PER Schumacher
6 WORDTAG O publicly
6 WORDTAG I-MISC Golf
50 WORDTAG I-MISC Iraqi
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Algeria
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Leeds
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Chonan
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Club
19 WORDTAG O rest
7 WORDTAG I-LOC AKRON
12 WORDTAG O King
3 WORDTAG O Rugby
53 WORDTAG O northern
10 WORDTAG O lifted
34 WORDTAG I-ORG Sydney
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Juan
1 WORDTAG O FC
50 WORDTAG I-PER John
40 WORDTAG O side
5 WORDTAG O cannabis
5 WORDTAG O imprisonment
5 WORDTAG O falls
6 WORDTAG I-PER Chamorro
507 WORDTAG O an
12 WORDTAG I-PER Patrick
4 WORDTAG I-ORG Cambridge
5 WORDTAG O partly
6 WORDTAG O auctions
8 WORDTAG I-LOC Bonn
7 WORDTAG O postpone
4 WORDTAG I-LOC DIEGO
5 WORDTAG O maintained
85 WORDTAG O Results
13 WORDTAG I-ORG Yorkshire
7 WORDTAG O via
9 WORDTAG O sees
6 WORDTAG I-PER Melissa
7 WORDTAG O personnel
14 WORDTAG I-ORG F.C.
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Australian
4 WORDTAG I-PER Brooks
37 WORDTAG O 27
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Hearts
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Volendam
11 WORDTAG I-ORG CDU
2 WORDTAG I-MISC Africa
6 WORDTAG I-PER Stevanin
5 WORDTAG I-PER Freeman
6 WORDTAG I-PER Dan
62 WORDTAG O found
13 WORDTAG I-ORG Milwaukee
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Norwich
7 WORDTAG O contracts
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Newsdesk
117 WORDTAG O 6-3
5 WORDTAG O 83rd
10 WORDTAG I-PER Armstrong
4 WORDTAG I-MISC County
10 WORDTAG O alliance
14 WORDTAG O 504
31 WORDTAG O rates
9 WORDTAG O aid
1 WORDTAG I-MISC for
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Rights
18 WORDTAG O secretary
55 WORDTAG O city
1 WORDTAG I-MISC law
6 WORDTAG O acting
1 WORDTAG I-PER West
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Dayton
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Escort
6 WORDTAG I-ORG PUNR
9 WORDTAG O reduced
10 WORDTAG O Government
2 WORDTAG I-PER (
84 WORDTAG O half
9 WORDTAG O jet
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Rican
20 WORDTAG O question
22 WORDTAG O problems
13 WORDTAG I-LOC House
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Kurd
15 WORDTAG O others
12 WORDTAG O stronger
20 WORDTAG O summer
17 WORDTAG O 1993
307 WORDTAG O I
6 WORDTAG O sometimes
9 WORDTAG O balance
6 WORDTAG O award
5 WORDTAG O Many
9 WORDTAG O visiting
9 WORDTAG O opportunity
8 WORDTAG O finance
7 WORDTAG O regarding
31 WORDTAG O death
9 WORDTAG O driving
53 WORDTAG O near
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Royal
5 WORDTAG I-MISC Democrat
1 WORDTAG O Central
7 WORDTAG O check
31 WORDTAG O coach
8 WORDTAG O blow
6 WORDTAG O speaking
59 WORDTAG O 64
13 WORDTAG O crime
8 WORDTAG O rescued
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Kurdistan
17 WORDTAG O track
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Raith
15 WORDTAG I-LOC Norway
4 WORDTAG I-LOC Charleroi
5 WORDTAG O acts
6 WORDTAG O gain
32 WORDTAG O further
15 WORDTAG O sex
35 WORDTAG O manager
5 WORDTAG I-PER Kontogiannis
15 WORDTAG I-LOC Beijing
5 WORDTAG O fix
255 WORDTAG O Wednesday
26 WORDTAG O south
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Swiss
9 WORDTAG I-MISC Baseball
40 WORDTAG O such
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Louis
16 WORDTAG I-LOC Chile
7 WORDTAG O newsdesk
13 WORDTAG I-LOC TORONTO
91 WORDTAG I-LOC China
17 WORDTAG I-LOC Berlin
5 WORDTAG O nominated
3 WORDTAG I-LOC PITTSBURGH
220 WORDTAG O when
6 WORDTAG O 86th
42 WORDTAG O head
11 WORDTAG I-PER Ferreira
35 WORDTAG O 29
105 WORDTAG O 70
1 WORDTAG O Union
19 WORDTAG O issues
5 WORDTAG O bushel
7 WORDTAG O transition
14 WORDTAG I-PER Daniel
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Luxembourg
31 WORDTAG I-ORG Ltd
1 WORDTAG I-PER Wellman
17 WORDTAG O form
54 WORDTAG O report
1 WORDTAG I-MISC Office
11 WORDTAG O mixed
14 WORDTAG O shortly
11 WORDTAG I-ORG Auxerre
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Cardiff
13 WORDTAG I-ORG Heerenveen
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Indian
31 WORDTAG O clear
10 WORDTAG I-MISC Singer
18 WORDTAG O life
42 WORDTAG I-MISC English
5 WORDTAG O planes
17 WORDTAG I-ORG Kurdistan
4 WORDTAG O Business
7 WORDTAG O amount
7 WORDTAG O attempts
30 WORDTAG O train
7 WORDTAG O Third
11 WORDTAG O means
8 WORDTAG O answer
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Games
5 WORDTAG O larger
6 WORDTAG B-ORG SPD
9 WORDTAG O assembly
5 WORDTAG O eventually
14 WORDTAG O NOTE
39 WORDTAG I-MISC Palestinian
7 WORDTAG O RECORD
23 WORDTAG O single
14 WORDTAG O veteran
5 WORDTAG O nominee
7 WORDTAG I-PER Black
34 WORDTAG O tennis
42 WORDTAG O like
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Milan
22 WORDTAG I-MISC Grand
7 WORDTAG I-LOC BANGKOK
8 WORDTAG O showing
6 WORDTAG O refined
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Bosnian
5 WORDTAG I-PER Bohdan
30 WORDTAG I-ORG U.S.
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Post
6 WORDTAG I-LOC BUCHAREST
32 WORDTAG O 96
16 WORDTAG I-MISC GERMAN
5 WORDTAG O 220
7 WORDTAG I-LOC Trafford
8 WORDTAG I-ORG Juventus
34 WORDTAG I-LOC Chechnya
9 WORDTAG O college
6 WORDTAG I-ORG CSU
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Miguel
27 WORDTAG O L
12 WORDTAG O First
19 WORDTAG O remained
6 WORDTAG O 1987
34 WORDTAG O order
7 WORDTAG O launch
7 WORDTAG O sterling
10 WORDTAG O WINS
10 WORDTAG O committed
40 WORDTAG O army
10 WORDTAG O Note
2178 WORDTAG O "
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Best
7 WORDTAG I-ORG Hamas
6 WORDTAG O 15-7
5 WORDTAG O shed
11 WORDTAG I-LOC Thailand
21 WORDTAG O cricket
18 WORDTAG I-PER P.
8 WORDTAG O Over
5 WORDTAG O unbeaten
18 WORDTAG O hope
154 WORDTAG O more
7 WORDTAG O successive
8 WORDTAG O concerned
11 WORDTAG I-ORG (
6 WORDTAG O worldwide
5 WORDTAG O crackdown
3 WORDTAG I-MISC Internet
6 WORDTAG I-ORG Sao
17 WORDTAG O pair
6 WORDTAG I-PER Rodriguez
8 WORDTAG O shows
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Alaska
1 WORDTAG I-LOC Carlos
21 WORDTAG O profits
9 WORDTAG O preparing
37 WORDTAG O best
75 WORDTAG O number
2 WORDTAG I-MISC Ten
10 WORDTAG I-ORG Ssangbangwool
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Istanbul
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Ballybunion
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Moslems
30 WORDTAG O details
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Corsica
6 WORDTAG O intended
10 WORDTAG O investigation
8 WORDTAG O extradition
356 WORDTAG O --
1 WORDTAG I-PER Sun
5 WORDTAG I-PER Prince
86 WORDTAG O They
15 WORDTAG I-MISC Windows
21 WORDTAG O stocks
6 WORDTAG O Income
8 WORDTAG O SQUAD
23 WORDTAG O offer
5 WORDTAG O autumn
3 WORDTAG I-ORG Pacific
5 WORDTAG O 59th
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Seoul
13 WORDTAG O responsible
2 WORDTAG O NEW
126 WORDTAG O Saturday
3 WORDTAG I-PER Louis
13 WORDTAG I-MISC RBI
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Arthur
10 WORDTAG I-MISC Serbian
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Four
92 WORDTAG O while
8 WORDTAG I-LOC Nicaragua
7 WORDTAG I-PER Liam
20 WORDTAG O votes
16 WORDTAG O recently
7 WORDTAG I-PER Stoltenberg
58 WORDTAG O deal
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Queen
7 WORDTAG I-PER Newcombe
56 WORDTAG O pct
78 WORDTAG O should
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Valletta
5 WORDTAG O grew
7 WORDTAG O 2001
16 WORDTAG I-LOC BRUSSELS
9 WORDTAG O rating
8 WORDTAG I-ORG MDS
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Rio
14 WORDTAG O 5-7
38 WORDTAG O strike
8 WORDTAG I-LOC COLORADO
5 WORDTAG I-LOC Cairo
5 WORDTAG I-PER Healy
13 WORDTAG I-LOC Arabia
4 WORDTAG I-MISC Two
8 WORDTAG I-PER Bourlet
1 WORDTAG I-MISC France
5 WORDTAG O inquiry
7 WORDTAG O missed
14 WORDTAG I-LOC Stansted
10 WORDTAG I-PER Mujtaba
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Mexican
6 WORDTAG O reach
5 WORDTAG O Trade
5 WORDTAG O spinal
8 WORDTAG O struggle
12 WORDTAG I-PER Yasser
6 WORDTAG I-LOC Boston
2 WORDTAG I-PER Key
6 WORDTAG O governments
21 WORDTAG O municipal
538 WORDTAG O his
8 WORDTAG O Scoreboard
8 WORDTAG O 280
19 WORDTAG O member
71 WORDTAG O international
7 WORDTAG O policies
32 WORDTAG O possible
6 WORDTAG O .504
26 WORDTAG O Total
8 WORDTAG O envoy
9 WORDTAG O delegates
8 WORDTAG O formal
15 WORDTAG O serious
26 WORDTAG O homer
6 WORDTAG I-MISC RUGBY
97 WORDTAG O n't
18 WORDTAG O 38
4 WORDTAG I-PER Nelson
7 WORDTAG O fled
7 WORDTAG I-MISC Kurds
5 WORDTAG O artillery
5 WORDTAG I-ORG Houston
24 WORDTAG O source
7 WORDTAG O catch
6 WORDTAG O except
2 WORDTAG I-ORG Indonesian
1 WORDTAG I-ORG Export
3 WORDTAG I-LOC Court
5 WORDTAG O insisted
12 WORDTAG O weekly
2 WORDTAG I-PER Hong
132 WORDTAG O other
21 WORDTAG O really
6 WORDTAG I-MISC S.
2 WORDTAG I-PER Jordan
